Inuyama Tamaki
Tachibana Hinano
Vspo
Tamaki (T): As our time is limited, how about we jump right into questions?
Hinano (H): Yes, that's alright
T: Ok, here we go
T: This is a fairly common question, but how did you two come to know of each other?
T: Hinano, do you remember when you first came to know about Inuyama Tamaki?
H: I don't remember that well, but as part of Vspo,
H: after my debut,
H: just going around; actually, I was originally really into vtubers
T: You liked them before your debut, right
H: Yeah, I watched them fair a bit
H: So I knew of your name
H: I didn't actually watch any of your videos or streams and such
H: But I knew of you originally
H: The first time I watched your stream was around...
H: Your 500k subs anniversary?
H: where you showed your 3D qipao (chinese dress)
H: and sung "Ikenai Borderline" with Kagura Mea
H: I thought, "This is nice." I remember "Ikenai Borderline."
T: You remembered that?
H: That's right! ww
T: I apologize.
H: Yeah, the two of you; Yeah, I didn't tell you ww
H: I thought that was really nice
T: I'm happy to be known from my dance and singing videos, but
T: with Mea, huh? That video was with Mea
H: Yeah, Mea-chan was there ww
T: Well, Mea is smart  and (??)
H: She's cute
T: Is that right? Don't "haw haw haw" at me
T: Well, it's good that you remember that song, but what about your current impression of me?
H: Now? Let's see..
H: I really like your appearance
T: Oh, really?
H: Yes.
T: Me, too, I really like Hinano.
H: ah...  (*/▽＼*) (*/▽＼*) (*/▽＼*)
H: ah, sorry, that was a bit-- (⁄ ⁄>⁄ ▽ ⁄ <⁄ ⁄)
T: How about we stop it there, since it'll seem too real
T: What? Do you want to go out with me or something? You going to confess to me later today?
T: You okay? I'm getting a bit excited. You alright?
H: I'm alright, sorry
T: Hinano's appearance is also right in my strike zone, so that's why..
H: Ah, thank you ( 〃▽〃)
H: I apologize, my otaku side came out, sorry.
H: It's hot in here! ( 〃▽〃)
T: Hinano! You're beet red! You alright?
H: Sorry, sorry!
T: I feel like it'd be dangerous if I push her any further, so
T: Well, regarding my impression of you,
T: the reason I came to know you was from your singing
H: Oh, is that right?
T: your cover of "When the First Love Ends", and, what was it
T: I completely forgot the name w
T: "Darling Dance"
T: I saw Darling Dance, and
T: well, I don't usually watch game streams
T: I thought you were really good at singing - a Vspo member who was good at singing
H: Ah, I'm glad
T: From there, well, I actually have a thing for menhera women
TLN: menhera comes from 'mental health.' It usually refers to women who are, e.g. clingy, obsessive, etc. You can't make this shit up.
T: Hinano-san's appearance is really, well, I wonder if the otakus understand ww
T: and, well, your appearance really fits my tastes
T: So, my first impression was that I liked your appearance and that you were a really good singer
T: But, now, well, I've actually come to watch a lot of your streams
T: And, it's already apparent in this stream, but you have a very hearty laugh
TLN: 豪快な笑い方
T: I love how coarse your language gets once you get used to someone
T: I really like that
T: Can I talk about the talk we had about the superchat you received yesterday?
H: Um, yes, it's fine ww
T: I watched Hinano's stream yesterday
T: Then, a superchat came, right?
T: It was a 250 JPY superchat that read, "Thank you for your hard work."
T: Then, Hinano was like, "Don't show off with just 250 JPY. I'm going to kill you," and then she blocked the sender.
H: No, I didn't go that far! ww
T: Okay, I added the "I'll kill you" part because it's what I wish she said
T: She said, "Don't show off", and then blocked them
T: That made me go, "Ah, when I superchat Hinano, it has to be at least 10k JPY. I should give 10k JPY for her anniversary."
T: But, when I asked her what that was about,
T: She said, "I only blocked them because of their name. I wasn't mad about the superchat itself."
T: That's right, wasn't it?
H: That's right. It was an otaku whose name showed their real face (?)
TLN: I'm not familiar with YouTube, but I guess she's referring to their profile picture? I don't see why that would be a problem...
H: So I killed them ww
T: So you killed them after all!
H: I did ww
T: So you did, after all
T: I see. So, anyway, I find that part of you really interesting
T: Bad-mouthed women are just kind of my thing, you know
T: Also, what is it, Hinano is really tsundere, right?
TLN: I doubt there's anyone who doesn't know what this means, but just in case. Tsun (=cold/blunt) + dere (cute)
H: No, no,
H: I think that that's rude to real tsunderes
T: What are real tsunderes?
H: Well, I mean,
H: I'm a pretty hardcore otaku myself
H: And, so, I have an ideal image of what a tsundere is
H: My ideal tsundere is Suzumiya Haruhi
TLN: From the hit 00s anime of the same name. Bit of a cult classic.
T: Ah, Haruhi, right, right.
H: And, I'm often told that I'm a tsundere, but, you know,
H: that makes me think, "I'm not Haruhi"
H: that's how I feel
H: and, so, when I'm called a tsundere -- What do you think I should do?
T: "What should you do?" ww
T: Personally, that reaction itself is plenty tsundere-like
T: It definitely registers on the tsundere radar
H: No way, what should I do..
T: I'd like you to stay the way you are
H: I understand ^^
T: Hinano is a proper tsundere
H: Is that right? ww