Inuyama Tamaki
Tachibana Hinano
Vspo
See link in the description for part one.
T: ..about our impressions of each other, but let's move on to the next question.
T: "What made Hinano-san choose to join Vspo?"
T: You talked about this in your interview, which I also read, but
H: Thank you very much
T: Regarding how you took the audition for Vspo,
T: but could we hear about the audition itself, as well as why you chose Vspo?
H: Ah, ok
H: This is, well..
H: It was really on a whim
T: You became a vtuber on a whim?
H: Yes ww
T: Nori, right?
TLN: Tamaki's actor's IRL first name is "Norio"
H: Well, my friend -- Originally, I was watching vtubers
H: There were a lot who played games
H: Around when I noticed there were a lot of gamer vtubers,
H: It was around the time PUBG was getting popular
T: Ah, that time
T: Around 2018 or so, right?
H: Yes, I was watching around then.
H: Well, I've always liked games, since way back
H: And I thought vtubers were cute, so I was like, "That's nice"
H: And, coincidentally, one of my friends told me, "Hey, this agency is hiring."
H: which turned out to be Vspo
H: As a result, I came to know of Vspo
H: And, well, there was an application form
TLN: 応募フォーム
H: But, by then, the deadline had passed
H: II realized that it had already been a week since the deadline, so
T:  Ah, but it was still open?
H: Yeah, so I got curious
H: I sent a Twitter DM to the Vspo staff, saying, "The form is open."
H: I sent that!
T: Why were you curious?
H: I was thinking, if somebody like me who wanted to apply but who noticed the deadline had passed,
H: if they applied anyway, I wanted to know what would happen
T: Right, since it'd be past due
H: Yeah, since it was past due, I was wondering if it was still okay
T: So you were taking care to not cause any misunderstandings, right?
H: Yeah, so I sent them a DM to let them know
H: And then, they replied with something like, "Thank you very much."
H: and, "We plan to leave it up permanently from now on. If you'd like, why not audition this round?"
TLN: 今後常設で...
T: Does such a thing even happen?
H: Yes, stop it! ww
T: A very unexpected development
TLN: 開始
H: And then, I replied, "If there's another opportunity, I'd like to apply."
H: At the time, on my Twitter or something,
H: I had an impressive video of my Apex gameplay
H: They might have seen that and thought, "This person's strong."
T: Ah, so they were like, "Wow this person's rank is crazy high."
H: Yeah, so they probably thought I was a girl who was good at games or something
H: They were looking for girls who were good at games who liked gaming,
H: so I think that's why they extended an offer to me
H: So, the interviews went like 1, 2, 3, and I ended up getting in
TLN: Tamaki mentions "なろう系" (naroukei, 'narou' -like), which refers to the famous web novel site, "syosetu ni narou ka," the birhplace of many manga and anime
T: Isn't that amazing? Are you some kind of light novel protagonist?
H: Yeah, I reallyam a light novel protagonist
T: The fact you were accepted like that is insane
H: I actually didn't think that I'd be accepted
T: So you were just like, "How about I give this a shot"?
H: I was going at it very lightheartedly
H: I was like, "Since it sounds like a good opportunity, why not?"
H: And, you know, for the audition, you have to send a short video, right?
H: And, I sent a shitty, effortless 30 second clip that only had audio
T: What's with that? ww
T: So it wasn't a video that you put effort in to produce?
H: No, it wasn't! It only had my voice, like,
H: I was like, 'blah blah blah'
H: So, after going on like that for a while, at the very end, I said something like
H: "I'm confident that, out of all the Vspo girls, I am the best at games."
H: I said something like that www
T: You're fucked up! ww
T: But, that's reassuring from the staff's perspective right? They'd be likie, "Wow, this one's something."
T: No, but, to be able to say something like that, you were one hell of a omwan
H: Yeah, I think it was that craziness that got me in
T: Well, for streamers, craziness is really important
T: So there was no mistake on the part of Vspo's staff
T: That could have ended up differently ww
TLN: 躱してる can also mean 'to evade/dodge (something).'
H: I'm glad ww
T: But, it's important to leave as big an impression as you can, right? Whatever the occasion.
T: I see
T: The reason why you chose your agency is really interesting
H: It's pretty amazing, right?
T: Yeah, it's pretty rare
T: Alright, well, the talk of how your audition went was quite shocking in itself, but
T: let's continue with this next question
T: "What were the streams or collaborations that were turning points for Hinano-san's career?"
T: Well, there's also the case where Hinano became known after getting banned, but
T: I think each streamer has their own causes of popularity
T: do you remember around when these events happened for you?
H: Let' see, the first.. well, there were two.
H: If we're talking about the reasons why I became popular.
H: The first was the CR Cup, which is a tournament hosted by a streamer, no, professional esports team, called Crazy Raccoon.
H: And, in that tournament, at the time, a streamer called SPYGEA (?)
TLN: I'm unfamiliar with all of this game talk, please do not hesitate to correct me.
T: As expected, even I have heard of him.
H: I was invited by him to a collaboration
H: I had the chance to enter the tournament along with him
H: And, as a result,
H: It was actually right after I had uploaded my cover of, "When the First Love Ends."
T: Ah, it was around that time?
H: And, SPYGEA-san teased me about it on-stream
H: As a result, listeners came to know about it
H: and the views increased by a ton
T: It has a lot of views, doesn't it?
H: Yes, I'm very grateful for that
H: That was the first reason -- is what I think, personally.
T: I see, I see.
H: The second was, well..
H: There is a group that I'm friendly with called the Comedian Brigade
TLN: Tamaki isn't even trying to hide it lmao
T: There isn, isn't there.
H: Among the members, there's a person called Kamito-san
H: And, with Kamiton-san, I... what should I even call it?
H: Well, it's simply, like, a collaboration
H: It's not a coupling (ship)
H: I say this all the time, but ww
T: It's a team name, team name
H: Yes, it's a team name made up of us two called "Orea and Apollo"
H: And, well, OreApo really, for some unknown reason,
H: I don't know why, but
H: It really, somehow
H: Became a hot topic
T: That, you know, is not for "an unknown reason."
T: You know, well, um, hmm, let's stop here.
T: S-sorry
T: I'm in front of Hinano, so I shouldn't say it. Let's take a chill pill with the otaku antics
TLN: オタク豪快, ie otaku excitement
T: It's really nice, so..  hmm..  yes... people will want to see more of it
H: It's pretty... Well, at the start, it was pretty..
H: I really didn't think it would become so big, honestly
T: yes, yes
H: At the start, we weren't able to communicate well with each other
H: You could say it was kind of painful to do so www
T: Was it like that at the start?
H: Yes, at the start, we were both like, "um.. uh..."
T: So it was like that!
T: That's really unexpected
H: Then, our listeners were, like,
H: "On the contrary, this is top-shelf content fumu fumu"
T: Ah, so they couldn't get enough of that feeling of distance between you two! I see!
H: That's right
H: Then, well, we thought, "Let's keep going and see how far we can go."
H: And, before we knew it, it became a big thing
T: But, the fact that you both wanted to go as far as you could, or,
T: that you both wanted to work hard together as streamers -- that's pretty amazing
H: Ah, that's true. We were able to get along very well
H: Yeah, we were able to get along well, and
H: and we both have two-toned hairstyles, so
H: that's something that's pretty rare among vtubers
T: Yeah, that's quite rare
H: Yes, it's rare, and
H: and, in addition to that, being able to get along was pretty amazing
T: Ah, certainly
H: And, well, OreApo was a really big turning point, I think
T: I see, well, about OreApo, I sort of
T: came with some questions about OreApo's beginnings**, but
TLN: 馴れ初め (なれそめ) = beginning of something, but usually romance
T: is it alright if I ask about that?
H: Wait, wait!
T: That said, allow me to bother with you just one question, thank you...
T: This is up my alley
H: No worries ww
T: I'm really sorry
H: No, no, it's fine
T: "You and Kamito-san have had arguments on-stream and on Twitter, but how frequently do these happen, and how intense are they normally?"
T: That's the question.
T: Sorry, can I say something
H: Go ahead ww
T: The real person-- sorry, sorry, sorry.
H: What is it? ww
T: I know it's gross, I'm really, really sorry.
T: There was time where you were, like, "Are you angry?"
T: And then, Kamito was like, "I'm not"
T: To which you said, "You're angry, aren't you!"
T: And then you both kept repeating, "Are you angry?" "I'm not!" "You are, aren't you!"
T: That was, well, uh.. uh.. in terms of 'the resolution' of a shipping.... I mean, you two are just a team.. uh..
TLN: 解像度 originally refers to digital resolution. In otaku speak, it refers to resolution/understanding of a character/personage.
e.g. having the same perfume as an idol raises your 'resolution' of them
T: Yes.. As I was watching that, I was grinning the whole time
T: That was, well, yes.. hm.. that, you know?
T: Yes.. well.. Sorry, my disgusting otaku side came out
H: Yeah... that was gross.
T: Hinano, Hinano, you're wrong, you're wrong!
T: That's not it, I'm the type of otaku who observes from the sidelines, but
T: Today, we coincidentally had the chance to work together
T: and I was going to stream with you, so
T: maybe I should stop this annoying interview?
T: Sorry, sorry, I just wanted to try being a bit aggressive and ask just one question like that
TLN: 攻め気
T: Well, that's right, there's cases where you have arguments on good terms, but
T: Well, what is the frequency of your arguments?
H: Frequency..
H: It's usually about games
H: We often have arguments about game-related things
T: You argue over that?
H: Like, when we're both simply very frustrated
T: Yes, yes
H: Like, "I told you that this was like that already, didn't I?"
H: Like, it's simply.. We argue quite often over things that happen in-game ww
T: Your reason for arguments.. that's really nice. Really, really nice.
T: It's really nice.
T: The resolution is exquisite.
TLN: See previous TLN on 'resolution.'
T: Wow, I'm getting shivers, wow.
T: That was great.
T: You can make a doujinshi out of this.
T: No, I want to draw it.
TLN: For those who didn't know, Tamaki is a professional mangaka.
T: I see.
T: So that's how it is. Ok. I get it.
T: Today was fun, thank you, really.
H: Is it fun?
T: Thank you. No, honestly, I was watching all kinds of videos right before we started today.
T: I was like, "Ahh, I see, I see," the whole time while watching.
T: (no explanation needed here, I hope)
T: The whole time, I was just going, "Ahhh," like an otaku
T: That's what happened
H: I don't like that...
T: Sorry!
T: I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
H: If I had to say whether this was gross or not, it's definitely gross.
T: I'm sorry! I get it, this is certainly something that makes the edges of our mouth stick to the ceiling, I apologize. I want you to be careful.
T: I apologize.
H: It's fine ww
H: I'm going to have a drink ww
T: Drink, drink ww