Tachibana Hinano
Vspo
Inuyama Tamaki
Noripro
We received this tip-off from someone
"I think Tamaki would definitely love to hear about how Hinano-san was a moderator for a major roleplay chat group, so please touch on that!"
Around two or so messages came saying the same thing.
Hinano-san... Tachibana-san, are you alright?
I'm alright
You alright?
I'm feeling dizzy
TLN: めまい
You ok?
TLN: 水分?
You should have a drink
Please wait a moment. This is pretty amazing
We received quite the recommendation
TLN: 特大おすすめ
Was Hinano formerly a moderator for a major roleplay chat group?"
I wasn't 'major' or anything, but..
ww it's fine even if you don't deny that part
whether you were major or not, both are fine
That's true. I didn't think that this information would spread this far
I want to punch myself in the past for casually divulging it
The phrase "roleplay chatroom moderator" is too impactful
TLN: She says that, but I'm the only person who has touched on this on the EN side of things.
Of course it would spread, right?
I just want to give my past self a punch
It's killing me
What kind of stuff did you do?
Umm..
Well, it was your standard roleplay chat.. group.. with various users and such..
And, well, if you were to ask what kind of stuff we did..
To explain what a roleplay chat is, it's a place
where you impersonate a character who you like
and talk with others doing the same
There were 10,000 users?
Wow, it was really big, huh?
No, I actually inherited the position
TLN: 引き継ぎ
Ah, so there was someone else who was doing it from the start?
Well, they'd be the previous generation moderator
Yes
Right, like 2nd generation, 3rd generation?
And, well.. ww
It was a chat where we'd impersonate characters from anime and manga
ww That.. How long did you do that for?
Like, 1 year, 2 years?
Ah, but..
I don't think it was a full year, I'm not sure..
The people there had been there for a while
So the users had been there for a long time
Yeah, the other users had been on the site for a long time, but
TLN: 加増
The site was fairly..
Like, other similar sites appeared
I see..
Certainly, with time, more and more roleplay chatting sites appeared, right?
I've never participated in online forums, but..
TLN: 掲示板. Think of 4ch, Reddit, etc.
Ah, right. There used to be something like an exclusive homepage for roleplay chats
TLN: Not JP, so I don't know what they're thinking of.
There was, right?
Wow, that's nostalgic
Stop bringing back strange memories
Stop it!
No, I can't
I can't, I can't
A lot of people are feeling the cringe right now
I feel the pain in my brain
What is this? I'm feeling assaulted from all sides here
I don't like it. I see. Well, there's a lot of history, right?
For everybody, right?
Alright, let's move on.
Should we move on? ww