Tachibana Hinano
Vspo
Inuyama Tamaki
Noripro
We received this tip-off from someone
"I think Tamaki would definitely love to hear about how Hinano-san was a moderator for a major roleplay chat group, so please touch on that!"
Around two or so messages came saying the same thing.
Hinano-san... Tachibana-san, are you alright?
I'm alright
You alright?
I'm feeling dizzy
TLN: めまい
You ok?
TLN: 水分?
You should have a drink
Please wait a moment. This is pretty amazing
We received quite the recommendation
TLN: 特大おすすめ
Was Hinano formerly a moderator for a major roleplay chat group?"
I wasn't 'major' or anything, but..
ww it's fine even if you don't deny that part
whether you were major or not, both are fine
That's true. I didn't think that this information would spread this far
I want to punch myself in the past for casually divulging it
The phrase "roleplay chatroom moderator" is too impactful
TLN: She says that, but I'm the only person who has touched on this on the EN side of things.
Of course it would spread, right?
I just want to give my past self a punch
It's killing me
What kind of stuff did you do?
Umm..
Well, it was your standard roleplay chat.. group.. with various users and such..
And, well, if you were to ask what kind of stuff we did..
To explain what a roleplay chat is, it's a place
where you impersonate a character who you like
and talk with others doing the same
There were 10,000 users?
Wow, it was really big, huh?
No, I actually inherited the position
TLN: 引き継ぎ
Ah, so there was someone else who was doing it from the start?
Well, they'd be the previous generation moderator
Yes
Right, like 2nd generation, 3rd generation?
And, well.. ww
It was a chat where we'd impersonate characters from anime and manga
ww That.. How long did you do that for?
Like, 1 year, 2 years?
Ah, but..
I don't think it was a full year, I'm not sure..
The people there had been there for a while
So the users had been there for a long time
Yeah, the other users had been on the site for a long time, but
TLN: 加増
The site was fairly..
Like, other similar sites appeared
I see..
Certainly, with time, more and more roleplay chatting sites appeared, right?
I've never participated in online forums, but..
TLN: 掲示板. Think of 4ch, Reddit, etc.
Ah, right. There used to be something like an exclusive homepage for roleplay chats
TLN: Not JP, so I don't know what they're thinking of.
There was, right?
Wow, that's nostalgic
Stop bringing back strange memories
Stop it!
No, I can't
I can't, I can't
A lot of people are feeling the cringe right now
I feel the pain in my brain
What is this? I'm feeling assaulted from all sides here
I don't like it. I see. Well, there's a lot of history, right?
For everybody, right?
Alright, let's move on.
Tachibana Hinano
Vspo
Inuyama Tamaki
Noripro
Should we move on? ww
Let's go with this..
Ah, this one piques my interest
"I think that both of you often say that you do not have a cute, or 'moe'-type voice,"
"and worry or have a complex about that, but.."
"I'd like to hear you two talk about that."
"Or, I'd like to also hear about ways you resolved these complexes."
Hinano-san, are you the type of 'human' who lacks confidence in their voice?
Ah, I very much lack confidence in my voice
Is that so
That's right
In the vtuber world, the majority of people tend to say,
or have the self-awareness, that their voices are cute
That's true
I haven't really met anyone
who says they aren't confidence in their voice
Ah, certainly
Well, there's actually a reason why I developed a complex about my voice
And, I've actually talked about it on stream before..
I was playing a game called Overwatch..
And, there's an in-game voice chat that anyone can join
When I was making a report,
someone told me, "Your voice sounds ugly"
"[keep that up and]  I'll troll." I was told something like that, so, as a result..
You -- That's terrible!
I thought my voice was ugly!
That's terrible! How could they say that?
To a girl...
TLN: Couldn't catch the second part. やめよ、やみの？
That's no good. That'd make you want to stop playing
It was just that one person, though.
Overwatch is a good game, okay?
Really.. what was with that guy..
But, really, I don't have a so-called  'cute' voice
No, no, that's not true
Ah, thank you
HInano's cute
You're cute, yup
You're properly cute
That's embarrassing.. (//▽//)
How about we stop being actually cute?
Let's stop being actually cute
So, well, I haven't actually resolved my complex
Even now, I still have a complex about my voice
Probably, people who watch my stream
and see this cute face -- they probably think
"Her face... doesn't match her voice"
I think that there's probably still a lot of people who think that
But that's their problem
It's no fault of your's
Certainly
That's how it is
This is my voice, I can't do anything about it
It's their opinion, Hinano's done nothing wrong
That's true. I've always had this voice and body
Right, you've always had that voice and body, they shouldn't say such unreasonable things
Yeah
What's with those people. Unforgivable.
Well, that's how it is
Well, now, it's like that, right? My listeners..
TLN: Enunciation isn't great, I think I hear "釣れて..."
Constantly.. they say they find my voice appealing
Like, they keep telling me, "You're cute," "You're cute."
Your listeners are kind, aren't they
They are (*ﾉ∀`*)
Well, they tell me that, so
Compared to before, things are definitely better now
I see
I'm also the type of person who doesn't have confidence in their voice
After becoming a vtuber,
everybody around me had such really, really cute voices
Everyone had a voice actress-like voice
Among a bunch of cute voices, my voice sticks out like a sore thumb
No, I get it
I was told that I was the only one with a nasty voice
TLN: JP nerds recognize the term ドブ from どぶろく. ie unrefined.
I was like, "Stop calling me 'nasty bot'!"
That's the worst!
When I was called the 'nasty voice bot',
I thought, "My voice sounds nasty, so it really stands out, huh"
That's what I thought
That's really terrible
And, well...
At the time, what another vtuber-san told me was,
"Your voice isn't nasty, but.."
TLN: 集団
"When you're in a group collab,"
TLN：迎合？　アドバンテージからの「アド」だと思う
"you have an advantage, so.."
"if you are a host or something, you'll stand out, so isn't it fine?"
I thought, "I see!"
I thought, "My voice really helps me stand out as a host, so.."
"I should just be the host."
So, I was able to take that constructively.
If I weren't told that, I'd probably think my voice was nasty
And, I'd be like Hinano when she felt shocked after being criticized in-game
Like, "Ah, so my voice is nasty..."
That's what I thought..
What is it..
That's nice
I think it definitely stands out
If I had to say whether Hinano's voice was deep or high, I'd say it's deep
And, when all the Vspo members are excitedly talking,
your voice would really stand out
That -- as a streamer, standing out
is really important, so..
So, isn't it a good thing?
TLN: Is this still アド？ Sounds like あと.
Yeah, our voices are advantages.
Then, let's be confident about them
Yes, let's
Well, complexes are pretty difficult to get rid of, so..
TLN: 言ってくれない？言ってくれる？ Not sure. I went with the first.
it's nice to have listeners not point that out
That's really true