Tachibana Hinano
Vspo
Inuyama Tamaki
Noripro
Alright, let's see what we have here..
"In the past, Hinano-san has said that, if Nazuna-san quit streaming, she would quit, too."
"Is Nazuna-san an important person to Hinano-san, after all?"
"What about Nazuna-san does Hinano-san respect?"
I actually read about this on your Wiki page.
I was really moved!
I thought, "She's such a nice kouhai!"
That information's out there, huh ww
And, well, is Nazuna-san an important person to you?
Yes, well, I don't really want to talk about it ww
Ah, she's getting embarrassed
To me, Nazuna.. -san...
I called her "Nazuna-san" www
Vspo was well, thanks to Nazu-chan..
Thanks to Nazu-chan and Kaga Sumire, Vspo was established
Since then, they've kept on going
And, actually, the way I interact with Nazu-chan is really casual
Isn't it, like, you're really close, so that's why your interactions are casual?
Yeah, well..
I  don't know if they're joking or not, since they're just words,
but there are often comments that say things like,
"Aren't you speaking impolitely to Nazu-chan?"
and, "Do you really respect Nazu-chan?"
People really say that?
I'm told that quite often ww
But, I really respect Nazu-chan, or rather,
I think she's amazing
She pays close attention to those around her
Like, she takes care of others.
And, if the agency is doing something, she'll take initiative to help out
TLN: 司会
Like moderating and such.
She's been, like, protecting Vspo for us this entire time!
TLN: Believe she's referring to Nazu news? Might have misheard.
Ah, she also does the news thing, right?
TLN: Not sure what the right term for this would be. Production seems general enough.
She's doing a lot of video production, which is really impressive
I thought her videos were produced internally
She's someone who works harder than anyone else.
Vspo's crazy impressive, right?
Yeah, Nazu-chan is really amazing
No doubt, that's very impressive
I really admire that part of her
So, I started talking with Nazu-chan a lot and quickly got to know her
which is why I treat her like I do now
But, well, we've talked a lot with each other
Like, we've actually gone out to eat together and such
In addition, it's, like, well... I can respect her as a person
But, of course there are times when she really irritates me
She can be annoying ww
Don't say that, don't say that ww
But, fundamentally.. Fundamentally, I like Nazu-chan
So, if Nazu-chan quit... I'd really hate that
As such, I've threatened to quit as well if Nazu-chan quit
Certainly, if Nazu-chan quit, you could say that Vspo wouldn't be Vspo anymore, right?
Yeah, definitely
That's amazing
But, Nazuna-san's even considered your daughter, right?
Yes, that happened totally without my consent
There's a father, mother, and daughter, right ww
She suddenly became adopted by me
Is that right? ww
She arbitrarily had me married and became my adopted child
Really..
That's too willful! ww
Really, that woman's crazy
Well, she has that humorous side as well, and
But, within Vspo, you're considered the 'mother' of Vspo, right?
And she became your daughter, right?
Right, there's something off about that person
We can say she's fairly free-spirited
I see, I see, we've heard something quite nice