Towa (T): Ah, crap, I forgot to bring tissues
T: Even though I'm out
Suisei (S): Out of what now?
T: Tissues. Tissues for my soundproof room.
TLN: 防音室
T: Since I ran out
S: You have a box in different parts of your house, right?
T: I do
T: Since it's annoying to have to go get it
S: I get that
Aqua (A): You have to wipe your nose sometimes right
T: You never know when a sneeze will come
S: That's true
S: I have one next to my computer
S: One in the kitchen,
T: One
S: One in the dining room, one in the living room..
S: One in my bedroom
S: Oh, and one in the bathroom/make-up room
T: Ahh
S: The washroom
T: The washroom?
S: Yup, two
T: I get it
T: They're especially needed in the washroom
S: They really are, aren't they?
S: When I do my makeup, I want to be able to
S: wipe off foundation that gets on my hands
body percussion tskr?
A: Makeup is done in the washroom, huh
S: No way! Where does Aqu-tan do her's?
A: mm... in front of the TV
TLN: The way Aqua says this line made me feel... something..
S: In front of the TV, huh?
S: You put a mirror there?
S: I see.. isn't it bothersome to have to grab a mirror (when you do your makeup)?
T: Yeah
TLN: Suisei says "盛れる," to make pretty, ie bathroom lighting makes you prettier
S: The washroom has the best lighting, though, doesn't it?
T: "best" ww
S: Yeah, it does ww
T: That so, huh
S: Yeah
T: Have you guys gotten afternoon tea before? Afternoon tea.
S: I haven't
A: I've gone before with Okayu
A: Ehe  (〃＾▽＾〃)
T: Fine, then, I'll just go with Sui-chan next time.
S: Ah, I'll go, I'll go!
A: Wait, wait, I want to go, too!
A: I haven't gone before~
A: What's afternoon like? I'd like to go.
T: Nothing new for Aqu-tan, I bet.
TLN: Towa says "感動がない," ie won't be impressed
T: "Amazing! So this is tea fit for the 'gram!"
TLN: Japanese slang, instabae, インスタ映え, ie "Instagram" + "attractive." Describes stuff that would get a lot of likes. Apologies for the pathetic attempt at localization.
T: Like, "This is lit"
A: Huh, what do you mean? What's that?
T: Like, "Bussin"
T: I want to make something "lit"
T: "So this is what it means to be bussin!"
S: Bussin ww
T: "This is lit~"
S: "Lit~"
S: That's a new species of fly
TLN: Fly in JP is 'hae,' which sounds similar to the 'bae' part of 'instabae.'
A: Insta bae?
S: There's a new species of fly called 'instabae,' you know?
A: Ahhh... sounds strong.