Yuzuki Roa
Kudou Chitose
(Roa) Regarding why we're here today,
I didn't think Chitose-chan was going to be able to stream today
(Chitose) That's right
Yeah, I thought Chitose-chan wouldn't be able to stream today, so..
We've only streamed together once
TLN: ちとろあ, ie "Chitose and Roa"
That's right. We were only able to do "Chitose and Roa's Adventure #1"
That's right
But we're doing it now
Yeah.. I thought we wouldn't be able to do this
And I also didn't do any preparations
I said that we'd make one last thing, so I said, "Let's make a grave," but..
Chitose-chan's busy, or, rather..
She had a lot of things to do/say, so
I had to do a lot of the prep myself
I thought that I wouldn't be able to make it in time
I saw
Yeah, so I was doing that
And, somehow
Somehow
Somehow..
Somehow, today, the two of us
Ah, it's looking pretty cute
Then, let's write messages
Do you want to make the stairway entrance look nice?
TLN: 変な段
Ah, but if we put carpet in front of the stairs, it'll look strange, so
This is fine how it is.
TLN: 無機質
The simplistic impression is good.
Then, should we write our messages here and call it a day?
Wait a minute, I'm going to flatten it
TLN: 平ら
Ah, wait. How do you write on this?
Oi, let me write.
Um..
Hmm.. what should I write? Ah, I shouldn't think too much.
Chibi, you're coming with us.
Ah, I made a mistake.
Chii-chan's cute!
Ah, where did Chii-chan go?
She ran away
She wants to sleep on the bed
Chii-chan's cute! She's sleeping on the bed!
Oh my, this is the first time I've seen this!
She likes being on the bed, you know?
It's my first time seeing this!
TLN: Nanoda's tl.
Oi, it's time for work!
Hey, can you hear her purring?
Oh my goodness!
I can!
ww we fell at the same time
It's beautiful!
Wow, it's so beautiful!
No way.. Amazing..
It's like a castle
It's really impressive
With this, it's finished.
We did it!
I might get sucked in ww
Wow, it looks so pretty.
Right? Should we take pictures?
Can you stand beside me?
I want to hold a flower.
Then, I'll hold onto some bones
Huh?
I'll stand to the left
Ah, just wait a second
Oh, there's a strange noise
It's hard!
Ah, this angle is pretty good
Here?
Yeah..
I'm holding onto bones! ww
Roa's holding flowers
You can't see that I'm holding flowers..
You're right
Wow, it's really beautiful
It's so beautiful
Isn't it nice?
It's really beautiful
We built this ourselves, but..
After..
Look over here. Then, should we end the stream?
Yeah.. we'll end the stream.
We did quite a lot, right?
Though it took some time.
That's right
Everyone, thank you for watching.
If we were able to make something as splendid as this...
TLN: 彫像
Ah, the statue's here..
Ok, then.. Wait, I'll take a screenshot.
I took one.
Wait a second, my game --
It's alright
Did everyone take one?
Did you?
Take one~
Ah, this is nostalgic!
Oh, it is! We did this before!
We did, didn't we..
TLN: I don't know why, but I strongly associate the phrase 「過言...」 with Kudou.
It wouldn't be an exaggeration to say that we met in Minecraft
Yeah, at the start... we got closer because of this, right?
How nostalgic
I was mostly playing by myself at the time
You were building your house somewhere else, right?
Yeah, and then, Chitose-chan came over, and..
That takes me back~
And, from that, we started talking more
Yeah
Then, should we call it here?
Again --
Yeah.
Let's talk again, okay?
That's right!
Yeah.
That's right..
Then, just give me a second, I'm going to set my OBS.
Thank you everyone for watching
Thank you
Oh, everyone's thanking you
Ah, thank you, it was my pleasure.
They say they love you, Chitose-chan.
Yeah.
I always love you.
AEIUO
Yeah, you know..?
You know... Starting tomorrow, Roa will..
It's, that..
I'll be...
I'll be alright, you know?
Yeah, I can see that.
Chitose-chan will be gone, but I'll be alright, you know?
Yeah...
Thank you.
That's it
That's it!