This is ranked!
It was, huh!
This is a battlefield
where anything can happen!
Sorry!
Sorry
What are you doing, going
and dying on your own..
Ah, that's how it is?
Yeah
Ok~
Gotcha~
The way you say 'Gotcha'
is really annoying
Gotcha~
Does that mean you like it?
Hinano language..
That's what it means..
When you say "That's annoying/Shut up,"
you mean, "That's annoying, but
I like it," right?
Well, well, well
Yes, yes, yes
You understand it pretty well, huh?
"Lame," too, is, "That's lame, but I like it."
Yeah ww
"But I like how you are,"
is what she means
Shut up!
wwww
You're too nice~
You're so annoying~
Hey, Bora-chan!
You mean to say,
"Look for safe areas!," right?
TLN: This is Apex lingo, which I don't understand
I can read you like a book
Annoying!
I'm going to eat Haagen-Dazs
What?! You, that's...
What flavour do you think it is?
Hmm... Hanamochi
TLN: JP-only flavour, it seems
Aah, you're wrong
Blueberry
Wrong!
Apple..
That's definitely wrong
Apple burgundy
Caramel
ww That's fancy, caramel
Apple caramel!
Apple caramel burgundy
The correct answer was... macadamian nuts!
Ah, we were close, though
Were you really?
First of all, do you know what burgundy is?
Hendy's relative
www
That's just because they
both have '-dy' in them!
Burgundy's a colour
It's a bit purplish, reddish
You're knowledgeable, huh?
Why do you know something like that?
Why do you think?
No way, could it be...?!
Could it be...?
What do you mean, "Could it be"?
You couldn't be...?
Did you really??
There's nothing interesting about this
Hey, hey
What?
You...
You've really done it now
What do you guys mean?!
There's a burgundy color for lipshade
TLN: lipshade, lipstick, lipgloss -- one of the three
A colour of lipshade?
Yeah
Ah, that's what you mean!
The cosmetics, you know?
Apple burgundy?
It's not apple burgundy, it's burgundy!
Burgundy, huh..
Wait, burgundy?
wwww
What? ww
Shut up!
www (but you like it)
Shut your trap!
You're so lame!
It's all Nun Bora's fault, really!
She's the worst!
She left and went off somewhere!
Don't fuck around, really
(but she likes it)
Messing around with me like she did..
That's probably the best way
to describe Hinano
Just recently, Bora-chan told me,
"I really like Hinano-chan's Sayonara Memories"
"and have been listening to it a lot recently."
So I said, "Thank you."
We occasionally message each other
[She's] cute.
It's emotional, Sayonara Memories.
Right?
Certainly
It is.
So she listened to it, huh?
Is there no one else?
"Is there no one else?"
Like, several days ago, on a members-only stream,
About half a month back, Hinano did an impression of me
I saw that
That kinda pissed me off
Why would you say
something like that?
wwww
Annoying~
You were sort of really energetic and, well, it didn't really resemble me.
I did resemble you
I did sound like you
What's with you?
I said, I sounded like you!
I sounded like you!
Why are you so baby-like?
I'm not trying to be like that, though
www (self-reinforcing laugh, 1, 2, 3...)
www Shut up
www
You're annoying, Q-chan~
"Whyyy..."
"Did I fall in love with you?"
You're noisy!
Ah, right. I saw that clip of you
with Bora-chan
of when you two
were playing together
Like, "You're annoying
(but I like you)."
Annoying
www but you like it
But you like it.
Shut up
But you like it! www
Hey! You're being gross, you know?!
Gross!
That's really lame
Annoying!
It's living rent-free in your head
No, not just in *your* head
Hey, can I play Fuse?
Okay~
Why Fuse?
Hm? Because I like him
I love this guy
You do, huh?
Yeah
Love him.
I also like Fuse
I like his bad mouthing
I like Fuse's face
His face?
For real?
Well, everyone has their
own tastes, after all
Right
Everyone's different, after all
It means she likes mature men, right?
Eh? You mean you're an
aficionado of old men?
TLN: フケ専
Hey, you
Why did you have to say that?
That's mean, isn't it?
Sorry
I thought that's how it was, so..
Even though I didn't want to
bring that up..
Ah, but, I sort of get it. I might like handsome mature men.
Like?
An example would be difficult
I didn't think you'd ask for an example
Ah, but you see..
Older men who are kind of cool are nice, aren't they?
Like, dandy older men?
Rather than 'older men,' ...
Hinano-senpai, please tell
us what your type is
My type?
I know it
What?
Wait, there's an enemy
Then let's stop
No, no, you can't
Wait, why? www
Why not?
Can't you just tell us?
No, I know you already know
From your reaction
You definitely know
what I'm about to say
What is it?
Can't you just tell us?
Kamito-san
Don't act all happy and shit!
Don't 'hehehe' me!
She definitely knew what
I was going to say!
Right?
I honestly thought that you actually knew what my type was.
Well, first of all, those without
dichromatic hair colours are
no good, huh...
TLN: Shinomiya uses a somewhat 'old-fashioned' word for 'two-toned.'
"Dichromatic" www
It's "two-toned," okay?
Don't say "dichromatic."
Don't say it as if you were a grandma!
"Your hair is dichromatic,
isn't it?"
But, the type of person I like...
But, they'll come eventually!
People with two-toned hair, that is!
Don't come!
They will, people with two-coloured hair.
That's not my type, though.
Ah, is that so?
Then, what is it really, your type?
For reference.
Hmm... well...
For starters, I like the colour white.
How white do you like them to be?
A sickly white.
Huh?
Hm? Were you just taken aback?
No, you're wrong.
A sickly white is good
A sickly white?
I'd like it if they were
skinny and had white skin
Hm? Wait..
You mean, you like
unhealthy-looking people?
Yes, yes, yes, exactly.
It's fine even if they have
eyebags and such.
BUT!
But, they need to have good hygiene
Like L? (Death Note)
Ahh.. that's right
(Noa): *crunch* *crunch*
Who's making those crunching noises?
N: Apologies!
Noa!
Kurumi!
What are you eating?
Ottotto
TLN: Japanese snack similar to Goldfish crackers. The word also means "Oops"
You're eating Ottotto?
What shape of Ottotto do you like?
There's star-shaped ones
That's starfish, right, not stars
What's your second-favourite?
Sunfish are cute
Sunfish, huh?
That's sunfish!
She's right
That one was correct
I like jellyfish
That's jellyfish!
No, she literally said "jellyfish!"
What's with that?
Jellyfish are cute
They seem really weak
Why would you say something like that?
Hey, hey, that's rude!
This is the first time I've met someone
who described crackers
as strong or weak
"They seem weak."
She said, "They look weak."
But, compared to other shapes, don't they look weak?
They don't seem like they'd be able to protect themselves
wwww
Can you really say that? ww
That's why, I feel like I want to
protect them.
You want to protect them, right?
Because they look cute, right?
Does Bora-san, like, when you look at people on the street,
do you determine their worth just from whether they look strong or weak?
Like, you look at someone on the
street and think, "Ah, they look strong."
"Their aura, it's different..!"
Hey, you're all noisy~
But, you like it.
But, she likes it.
There it is!
Don't "There it is!" me
It's Bora-chan's fault, you know!
Because of Bora-chan,
whatever I say, people tell me, "But you like it."
But you don't dislike it, right?
mhmm..
She was just like, "////"
Ah, slashes, huh?
"/////"
Shut u-- Let's get going!