Yakumo Beni
Kaga Nazuna
Hanabusa Lisa
Ichinose Uruha
I'm going to have some dried seaweed
Okay
Please tell us how it tastes
It's good
How so?
It's sour but you can still taste the kelp
Ah, how nice. You're good at reviewing food, aren't you?
Then, I'll do one, too
On what?
I'll be drinking Evian water
Evi- E- E- E-... Ah, ok.
This is... soft water, isn't it?
Evian is soft water, indeed
You know your stuff, huh?
I've drunk it before, so yeah (*smug*)
I just said something random, though ww
If you drink hard or soft water, it seems like you'd be able to tell which is which
You wouldn't!
No, but, normally, all you drink is soft water, right?
Since you don't drink soft water right after drinking hard water,
but if you did, you'd be able to distinguish them
Which is hard or soft.
That so?
I'm drinking hard water right now
Apparently, hard water makes you go, "This is hard!"
"Ah! This is hard!"
Yeah. You'll be like, "This water is hard!"
"This water is... hard!"
[Reading comments] Apparently.. Evian is hard water...
wwww
Don't mess around, you!
I feel embarrassed! I feel my face reddening..
That's really embarrassing, you know?
You should feel ashamed ww
What, what?
Evian is hard water?
Lisa was like, "Evian is soft water, isn't it?"
Then, Nazu-chan said, "Oh, you know your stuff, huh?",
so Lisa said, "I've had it before, so yeah", but...
Really, you...
Lisa, stop it, really, I'm feeling embarrassed, Lisa-chan~
I'm the one feeling the most embarrassed here..
I can't trust you anymore
Sorry..
You're cute, Lisa-chan. I like that part about you
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
That's how it is, right?
I'm just going to stop talking, alright?
No, I feel you, I really do.
Right?
The way you spoke so smugly
Yeah, yeah
I've had enough of living, already.
Water overseas is mostly hard water.