Kitaoji Hisui
Nijisanji
June 25, 2021
There's quite a lot of Otaku speak,
but, don't worry, Tamaki
explains everything very clearly.
Inuyama Tamaki
Noripro
Ok, let's start with this one..
"Please tell us about how you two got to
know each other and your first impressions of each other."
About this, well, Inuyama Tamaki's 'mother'
is a mangaka called Tsukudani Norio-sensei, but..
I heard off the grapevine that you
may or may not know about that...
It was a while before I put
two and two together!
Oh, you didn't know that
my mother was Norio-mama?
That's right!
Is that right?
Then, how did you come to
know about Norio-mama?
Well, I was at a particular 'aopu'
Please stop, don't use that word here.
I'm the only one here who knows what that means.
Nobody knows what 'aopu' means.
Could you first tell us what the anime it was from?
Yes. I was at an Inazuma 11 doujinshi event, and
That was a very good anime, right?
it was there that I had the chance to learn of you
TLN: the word for young/youth is 'seishun,' the first character of which can also be read as 'ao.' The 'pu' part comes from 'kappuru,' i.e. couple.
The Inazuma 11 event was named 'aopu,' an abbreviation of 'young couples.'
Yes, 'aopu.' It's not 'seipu,' it's 'aopu.'
Even though it's 'young (sei) couples,' right? How mysterious.
Yeah, so, I participated in the 'young couples' event
So, at the time, did Hispi-chan go there to make purchases?
Yes, at the second AoPu event, I went to buy some things
And I sort of parted ways with a friend
because the couplings/ships we liked were different
Oh, is that right?
Yeah
For me, it was 'tenkyo'
If you say 'tenkyo,' nobody will know what that is
Stop it!
If you say that, we're going to talk about it, so, really, stop it.
'TenKyo' is.. Tenma-kun and.. Kyosuke-kun, right?
So there were books about those two.
I'm talking as if everybody understands.
No, nobody does.
But, by the way, you're... in middle school, right?
I am.
At the time of 'Young Couples' (the event), Norio-mama was..
Let's see.. it should have been around 11th or 12th grade, so..
She (Norio-mama) was around 17 or 18 at the time, right?
Yes.
Now, Norio-mama is 27 bordering on 28, so..
Altogether, that means it's been about 10 years..
So, you were around 4 years old... ?
No, no, I'm 14.
You went when you were 4 years old, right?
I'm 14.
You're 14 now, and you went when you were 14, right?
Yes
Ah, I see
Being virtual is convenient, isn't it!
You can age from 14 to 14! ww
*dying*
Are you okay? Everything's fine?
Are you really alright?
I'm actually 14, though.
Of course, we can't see anything right now that would indicate otherwise, after all.
All I'm seeing right now is a very cute high school , middle school, girl.
Yes.
Ok, well, continuing the 'Young Couples' story,...
You were there to buy books about Tenma-kun and Kyosuke-kun.
Yes, yes
And, my friend was into 'RanTaku'
Stop it, okay? That's short for Ranmaru-kun and Takuto-kun
I know you'll explain it, so I'm relying on you
Don't make your senpai have to cover for you!
Anyway, there were characters called Ranmaru-kun and Takuto-kun
and there were books about that pairing
And, Norio-mama drew some of those books, right?
That's right. And, well, thinking about it this way..
I'm a diehard stan for my ships, so I didn't really..
Will they understand what 'diehard stan' means? Really...
That is, you were somebody who didn't care for ships besides Tenma-kun x Kyosuke-kun
TLN: uuuh.... I think it's pretty clear what is meant here. Recall the old adage, "one for using, one for reading."
Yeah, but, besides that, I'd gladly eat anything
Wait. Don't say "eating," okay?
I'm having to retort to everything you say!
That is, you were omnivorous -- you were willing to read anything.
Yes, yes. So, I had the pleasure of reading such books.
And then, at that time, they were there.
You mean Norio-mama's books, right?
That -- I saw Gundou-sensei's tweet and thought, "Wait, what?"
Well, to explain, there is a liver called Gundou Mirei-sensei
and she seems to have also bought Norio-mama's Inazuma 11 doujinshi
TLN: I believe the word is 内輪
Previously, on Twitter.. Well, there was a gathering, right?
And, if I recall, we were both there, right?
That's right
I see.. you saw something you shouldn't have..
ww there's a chance that the three of us were in the same place at the same time
That's a little fun to think about
At the time, Nori-mama was there, selling the books and acting as the salesgirl
so there's a chance I handed one to you personally
There is! ww
That's scary!
Furthermore, only around 200 copies were sold
So there aren't a lot of people who could have been there
In the first place.. that's too scary to think about..
So that's how the two of us became connected
Wait, it's starting to be fun talking about Inazuma 11, could we stop?
So it was then that you knew about Norio-mama, right?
Honestly, what made me put two and two together was Gundou-sensei's tweet
Ah, so, before that, you had no idea?
Yes, I really had no idea!
Ah, so you also weren't aware of how I was taking over the Vtuber world?
I didnt...
Let's take back what you said just now
Say that there's no such thing, okay? You're my kouhai, right?
"There's no such thing~"
Is that right? I see. You're really nice, aren't you?
Hispi-chan is such a good girl, I'm glad.
I see.
It was a collab with Yumeoi (Kakeru).
Oh, him, huh?
Which Yumeoi collab was it?
He's been in so many collabs that I have no idea which it would be
Let's stop trying to remember
Let's stop!
Yeah, how about we stop
I'm starting to feel scared
This woman has a tendency to say outrageous things, so I'm starting to feel a bit nervous
So that's how you got to know about me, but did you have any first impressions?
Hmm.. I thought your appearance was insanely cute
Oh, really? Certainly, my face is something that Norio-mama gave birth to, after all
Also, I.. that small, fluffy thing..
I like it. The thing on top of your head.
Oh, the mascot-like thing?
Yeah, I bought it!
Huh? The plushy?
So you were a fan...
It's just lying over there
It's really cute, right? It's really big, right?
It's really cute. It's perfect as a pillow.
Please don't use it as a pillow
The plushy on top of my head -- we've made it into a plushy and are selling it as merchandise.
Wow, you really bought it?
That makes me happy, honestly.
I'm glad..
I see, I see
Then, about how I got to know Hispi-chan..
TLN: Selejo is the name of Hispi's cohort in Nijisanji, aka Selene Girls' Academy Drama Club
Well, I watched all of Selejo's debut streams
because I try to watch every Nijisanji liver's debut stream.
and, well, I knew of you from there.
But, well, how I actually got to know about you was
(After your debut) there was a sudden announcement about a collab with Maimoto-kun
titled "Teach me, Mai-Mai." and it had a hellish thumbnail
it popped up in my recommendations, and
I was like, "W-w-what is this?"
I thought, "Maimoto's got involved with yet another woman.."
I was like, "What is this.."
No, really, what was that
I was wondering how you two would interact, but realized, "Ah, he's sort of like her plaything."
I thought, "Huh, these two managed to get fairly close, huh?"
So I had a fairly good impression of you.
Then, my first impression of you from your debut stream, was
that you were cute, but I was spacing out and didn't really make note of anything
but from there, seeing how you began teasing Maimoto...