Kitaoji Hisui
Nijisanji
Hoshikawa Sara
Okay, next
"Can Hoshikawa and Hispi talk normally with their ex-boyfriends?"
"It's awkward meeting them in places like the train, but what should you do?"
Cute..
Cute.
The kaomoji, you know? It shows they have good taste.
Can you talk to your exes?
I can, but..
Like, if I meet them in the train or something..
I can talk to them -- If they talk to me, I can.
Though, I don't think of my exes as human beings in the first place.
I think of them as human trash, so..
It's like, "Ah, there's a bottom feeder who I rid myself of." ww
Something like that! ww
So strong! (mentally)
That's how I think about them, so..
Like, I have no qualms talking to them
It doesn't really feel awkward
I see.. For me, it probably depends on how we broke up
Are there awkward ways of breaking up?
Yeah, like, if they cheated on you or if you had a fight and broke up..
If it's something like that, I'd look at them as if
they were garbage and switch to a different carriage
I see. Certainly, you don't want to be around them
But, by and large, we stay friendly, so I can talk to them normally
Conversely, how do you break up so that you remain friends afterwards?
Well, it's like, "This isn't right"
Like, we both get along really, really well, but..
when we start to no longer feel attracted to each other..
I see.. That's the best, right? You could still talk to them
after breaking up, like if you met them in the train or something.
Well, those are fairly rare..
They seem pretty rare, right? w
But, if you were 'normal,' then it might not be so rare.. www
TLN: 'menhera' typically refers to 'crazy' women, e.g. overly clingy, etc. It's often used in a self-derogatory way, but also as an insult.
I'm sort of taking a menhera's perspective
That's a world that's beyond reach for a menhera
This really depends on the individual, whether you can talk to your ex.
But, you know, if you got into a new relationship..
You wouldn't want to talk to your ex, right?
Honestly, exes are the worst
That's right
That's true, really
From the perspective of the current girlfriend,
I'd want the ex-girlfriend to just die.
Same!
I mean, the ex was somebody they really liked, right?
This sounds rude, but, honestly, I'd want them to fuck off somewhere else
TLN: 存在をちらつかせる. Couldn't think of a better TL.
I don't want their ex to flirt with them
Don't show your face around us
No, really... That's right, be careful..
I don't want to hear from someone I'm dating talk about their ex
Are there people who do that?
There are!
A boyfriend talking about their ex-girlfriend?
Yeah
Do they bring that up?
Do men like that exist?
There are
For example, what do they talk about?
Well, like...
Like, "Oh, I've been here with my ex-girlfriend."
*dies*
You wouldn't even say that as a joke, right?!
Wait, no way..
You wouldn't say that -- Would you?
Even if you were at such a place?
Wouldn't you say it's your first time, even if it's a lie?
I would say that (it was my first time)
What do you mean? That you've been there before?
No, not that
I'd say it's my first time. Even if it wasn't, I wouldn't say so.
Those types of guys are scary
Awful..
Are there no guys who say that?
There aren't those types of people, normally
What? No way
That's no good
It is, right? Isn't Hispi's taste in men strange?
Help me!
That's crazy..
"They broke up with their ex-girlfriend because"
"they lost interest in them, so isn't there nothing to worry about?"
Y-O-U A-R-E W-R-O-N-G!
That's totally wrong!
Y-O-U A-R-E W-R-O-N-G ~
you are wrong~
That isn't how this works
Even if it was brief, the two of them shared happy times together
Regardless of how they broke up, this is irrelevant
It's irrelevant
I don't like that they still have memories of each other
If they're the type to let everything go, then I'd be totally fine with it, though
In fact, I'd want them to badmouth their ex
I get it!
I get it, I really get it!
TLN: My poor fucking ears... have mercy...
I want them to be like, "My ex-girlfriend was disgusting"
Same, I'd want them to say that! I'd say that, too!
Me too!
"Ah, my ex-boyfriend was gross!"
I would, I definitely would!
I'd want them to tell me things that harshly degrade their exes
But, you know, women tend to think that their exes are gross, but..
Men, like, you know? They don't really think that about their ex-girlfriends.
That's how they are, or so I arbitrarily opine.
If that's the case, then the guy is just a pussy
That so?
Really?
TLN: From here on, they keep moving away from their mics, so there's a few lines that are hard to hear.
You often hear people say (??), right?
Yeah, I also often (?). That's no good~
That's really no good
Does that mean it's better to date somebody effeminate?
Ooh.. have you met someone like that before?
No, not really
Same
I only know people who are sick and effeminate.
That sounds a bit dangerous
Even when I talk to my male friends, I don't think there are many people like that
Everyone's living their own lives
Why do guys keep their exes' LINE info?
What? Where, where?
In the comments
"Why do men keep their exes' LINE.."
Oh, is this about their exes?
If they keep it, that's bad!
I'd hate that!
Gross~
Delete it~
What would you do if you got a message like, "What's up?"
Exactly
"If they badmouth their ex-girlfriend, isn't that off-putting in itself?"
Like, well, if you're around your friends, right?
Like, you're in the classroom with a large group of people
if you say, "God, my ex-girlfriend was such a bitch." -- that's a turn-off.
But, if you're in front of your girlfriend and say something like, "My ex-girlfriend was a bit.."
"Honestly... she was bit nasty, a bit annoying. I didn't really like her. I don't like her."
I want them to hate their ex...
I want them to only say it in front of their girlfriend
You want yourself to be number one
Right?
Isn't that, like... menhera?
We're comrades, huh?
Wait, but, don't all women feel this way?
Don't they?
I think they do
It doesn't have anything to do with being menhera..
"It's troublesome to delete it." No, you should just delete it.
"I didn't necessarily add them because we dated."
Their LINE.
What do you mean?
Like, the reason they had their ex's LINE in the first place wasn't because they were dating
Like, they exchanged info as friends
Oh, so they were in the same group..
So what?
So what? What's the deal?
If you delete it --- Just delete it.