"I am the master of my, as well as your, destiny."
"The master of your destiny"
It's written as 'destiny,' but don't you read it as 'fate'?
Hey, it's alright if you get
mad at him, you know?
You...
You're really..
I'm literally going to find out where you live
and disconnect your Internet
Honestly, Hanabusa, I think you're really amazing
What is?
That isn't something a middle schooler can write, you know?
Shut up! Shut up!
No, it's really impressive
It's really cool, like..
There's a story to it and all
You're annoying!
You know, what I thought was amazing was, "White Memory," ...
Hey! This guy is hella annoying!
He is, isn't he?
TLN: Not quite a full sentence here
Like, the lyrics properly have "White" in them
But, listen,
"White Memory" is a work that
was inspired by KagePro, so
TLN: I was 17 when all this was happening. How times fly.
It'd be "Lisa (Shizen no Teki-P)," right?
That's the perfect duo, isn't it?
"Then, suddenly, a truck [struck] you..."
Back then, I was ...
*kagerou days*
Back then, I used to think white earphones
looked good on me,
L: so I went around feeling good about that
"With white earphones on..." (Children Record)
It's so nostalgic, I feel like I'm going to die
I feeling the most embarrassed here, though?
I kind of want to try meeting Hanabusa from back then
No, can you really stop it
Don't come anywhere near me
"Don't come anywhere near me," she said! www
That, and, I'll go, wear a hood,
With your eyes covered up, too?
When I was really into KagePro, I thought that
everyone who wore their hoods indoors were KagePro fans
That's crazy ww