Our rank was always quite good, right?
It really was!
Why do you think that is?
Hmm.. because everybody's strong!
Well, there's that, too, but..
It's because Kamito's moves were amazing!
Wooow!
Can I order (Uber) now?
Hm? Go ahead
TLN: Sorry, too lazy to TL everything she says
By the way, if I order Uber, it
might come during a match, but even so..
No, that's fine
I complimented him, but he ignored me, huh?
No, it was hard for me to reply
Do you not handle compliments well, by any chance?
Ah well, I, uh, I, I, I'd say that I do..
wwww
What, what, what?
Actually, I wasn't sure what to do
What about? What you're going to
do with the rest of your life?
No, it's because you two
were like, c- c- c-
Like, kind of, c-casually saying it
I had the option of saying it was all thanks to you  two
Or, I could be like, "Yay, all me, all me"
and be very arrogant, but I wasn't sure which I
should have gone with, so
I ran out of time to reply, so
I thought, "Replying now would be kind of...,"
Gross
Hey, hey, you're flapping your gums a lot
wwww
Kinda weird, ngl