Lize Helesta
There was a time when Ange invited me out for pancakes -- can I talk about this?
It was a really nice shop, and, when the pancakes arrived,
well, we went to a well-known shop and both ordered banana pancakes, right?
our orders arrived, and we saw a stack of three pancakes
at the very top, there was a piece of banana
and, while I was going, "Wow, this looks really, really good!"
Ange took the piece of banana and
put it all in her mouth in one bite
I thought that it was a fairly large piece of banana, but
when I saw her eat it all in one bite, I thought, "Wow, she's really into it."
As I was thinking that, I saw Ange go completely silent
When I moved to try the banana for myself,
She said, "Lize, stop. You can't eat it."
"This isn't banana."
"It was butter."
I feel really bad that I can't show you guys pictures, but..
The round object on top of the pancakes that Ange and I both thought was banana --
It was round. Round, not square-shaped.
That round object was.. butter ww
Ange swallowed the butter whole ww
TLN: 丸呑み
In one bite ww
But, the reason why I can't blame her is
it really looked like banana
We ordered banana pancakes, and
the butter that comes with pancakes is usually square-shaped, right?
But these were round!
TLN: 輪切り
Certainly, I thought that the banana pieces looked a bit bigger than usual, but..
TLN: 平らげた, 一通り
And, after, when we spread the butter out over the pancakes,
Ange was like, "The butter disappeared!"
She got really mad over the fact that the butter was gone
TLN: 瀕死
I was laughing so hard that I thought I was going to die
Then, when I asked her, "Do you want half of mine?"
She said, "No, I'd feel bad."
TLN:　課金
So, I said, "You should ask the staff to give you more butter, even if it'll be billed."
Then, Ange was like, "No way, how could I? What would I do if they saw me?"
"They'd be like -- She just swallowed a whole block of butter whole and is asking for another..?"
"Something's wrong with her!"
I was like, that's true ww
That's true, if the staff saw her ww
When Lize and I were about to go home
From eating pancakes
Yeah
Yes, yes
I accompanied you to the train station, right?
Yes, you did
Yeah
Then, I was thinking that we'd just part ways normally, but
Just when I was about to leave, I looked at Lize's face and
saw that she was literally on the verge of tears
Like, I had never seen her make that sort of face before
She literally had tears in her eyes
That's wrong!
No, we weren't going to be able to meet again for a while
I wasn't going to be able to see her again for a while due to circumstances
So, after, we weren't able to meet for a while
We weren't able to meet, right?
That's right.
It's not as if I cry everytime we part ways, alright?
Right, you're not like that everytime, but..
it was a sight I had never seen before, so..
This is the worst!
It made me really agitated
I was like, "Huh? What? What should I do?"
Yeah, like, I'm generally not very fond of physical contact, but
I immediately went in for a hug
We did, we did!
Right? We hugged each other, right?
We did ww
We did!
We were like, "We'll meet again," or something ww
Yeah, that really made me feel uneasy
That happened, didn't it...
Oh, haven't you said before, like,  you dislike touching or
being touched by other girls? You have, right?
Yeah, but, rather than dislike, I didn't know what to do
TLN: Lize doesn't finish her sentence here, so I'll try to guess
You don't like the clingy types, right?
I did that on impulse
That was really surprising
I was really surprised
That... I felt really uneasy back then. It left a very strong impression on me.
That happened, didn't it...
"Please play the 'I love you' game with Ange. If embarrassed, please recite the Helesta multiplication table."
The 'I love you' game?
I'm not sure, but I think that we say 'I love you' to each other
Huh, what? What happens if we do [say that]?
TLN: 錬成
It's embarrassing... I don't want to..
But, when I picked up this Marshmallow, I looked up what this game was about
and, well, it's a party game you play with
lots of people, not with just two people, right?
You can't? When I saw a girl and guy do it, I was like, "What the hell?"
Why did you think that?
I was jealous...
"The first person to feel embarrassed loses." What's the 'first'?
Is it not over in one turn?
Ah, right, right
Three times? Huh, was that not it? Maybe I'll look it up
You takes turns and each person does it three times, so it's like, three times, three times, etc.
So you face off three times?
Yeah
Why is it three times?
Is that wrong? Maybe it's not three times. Maybe it's just once.
Oh, it's true. In the real thing, participants form a circle or something
Once per person?
So, one person... says "I love you," and
then, the other person has to say, "Sorry, could you say that again? I couldn't hear you."
Ah, like, "Oh, I couldn't hear what you said~"?
Yeah, yeah. Then, they say it again, and if the person saying it gets embarrassed, they lose.
TLN: 後攻、有利
Then, doesn't the second person have the advantage here? I won't lose, probably.
TLN: 前提
Why are you assuming you'll be the second person?
Oh, that's because I'm going after you.
Why? ww
Wait, so, the person listening just has to go, "Hm? What?", right?
Then, it'll never... Let's go to two rounds.
How does that work? If nothing happens to me, then what? Do I win?
We'll each have two turns, then we'll switch. You'd take my place.
Okay, got it. Then, show me what you've got.
I'll start? Are you serious?
Are you serious?
Wait, wait! What's up with you?
It's just a game, right?!
No, no, I got it, I got it.
Are you really alright?
Leave it to me, don't worry, it'll be fine
Something bad is going to happen
Just wait, I'm going to do it
Wait, what?
What? Wait, stop it! I'm going to say it!
I'm about to say it!
Your audio's breaking up
Sorry, excuse me
TLN: ムキ
I got a little worked up
I love you.
You lost!
You lost, alright? You've lost.
I still haven't lost yet.
Is this perhaps a one hit KO for me?
What?
Was that a one hit KO just now?
No, no, that was just a sample, so..
I was just surprised. I was adjusting our volumes, so..
I also just lowered my volume
I was adjusting our volume, so..
Ok, here I go
You're doing it again -- ah, okay.
Then, how about you try?
Ah, uh, um, just wait. C-can I mute myself and try it once?
What is this waiting time...
I can hear her going 'un..'
Are you back?
Here I go
The bar's higher
Stop it, really
Ok, here I go. I'm going to say it, alright?
I'm really going to say it, okay?
Bring it.
Just wait. Just wait ww
Am I not allowed to say anything besides, 'I love you'?
TLN: Ange is probably showing her a website or something, since they're together IRL right now.
No, that's fine, like, normally, it's like this or that, but..
Huh why did you just make it harder?
Because, you just...
You just asked what other things you could say instead ww
I think it's fine if you say something else
Ah, I'm feeling sick. I'm going to die. I'm feeling sick.
Ah, wait, this --
Reciting the multiplication tables would have been better...
Still? We don't have much time, you know?
TLN: つむる
Wait, my eyes --
Here I go. I'm going to say it!
Don't actually close your eyes, please
I didn't say I would, okay?
Here I go, I'm going to say it.
TLN: 生唾飲んだ
I actually just swallowed my saliva
No, well... I love you, okay?
Didn't I win?
What? Why are you looking dead with your eyes half-closed?
Why are you looking dead with your eyes half-closed?
Was it just lag?
No, that was my serious face.
Thank you very much
Please take care of me in the future as well
Yes
Then, this is really the end.
Is it the end? That's insane
The end of LizeAn week...
It's the end, so..
That's crazy
Let's stop
Let's stop. Don't think too deeply
Let's stop. Okay.
Then, from July 1st through July 7th, and, as the date has just changed, 8 days total.
Thank you very much for accompanying us this entire time.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much. We are very happy.
Sweet dreams, good night!
Good night! See you later!
Bye bye!
Did you read the description?
What did you write there?
Should I read it?
Go ahead
It was a long but brief week.
We may have been friends for 10 years, but you could also say that we are strangers.
I thought that there would be at least one thing that wouldn't work out, but
it was a week that was filled with nothing but dream-like happiness.
Ange, truly, thank you very much for the past week.
Stop it! I thought you were going to tell a joke or something, stop it!
What's with you? Ehh?
Stop it, stop it