Yashiro Kizuku
Nijisanji
Sasaki Saku
Somehow, it feels like it's been a while
Right? We've went to a lot of business trips lately, after all
Yeah, I even forgot where the studio for Lever Gacha Daipan was
What was that room again?
Events and such.. they were fun
It was fun
So monotone
Why did you sound so emotionless?
I don't remember any of that, though
Don't actually admit you did it
It seems like, guests..
It's our first guests in a while
It's Fall now, so
some autumn-like guests may have come
What does 'autumn-like' mean?
Those who seem like they like acorns
Ah, those people!
Would it not be a black shiba?
So they like acorns? ww
Nobody's here, though
W-why?!
S-since when have you guys been here?!
Thanks for your hard work
何食わぬ顔
With that suspicious look on your faces!
Where'd you come in from?
We've been here from the start
From the start?!
No, but, we were sitting right there!
N: Our guests this time are...
N: he's scary.. is he a guy? It's Mashiro, and..
N: Cannibalism Akabane-san
Hi, hello, good afternoon, it's Mashiro
I'm always doing scary things, but, today, I'll be representing 'calmness'
He's gone and started
He's already lying
I'm not lying!
Hi, konbane, it's Akabane Youko
Today, I'm also representing calmness and will be seiso
You're both lying
Then, today's going to be a day free from scary things
Ah, so there won't be any surprises today
Yeah, but, I'm glad to finally be here
Oh, did you happen to want to come?
Yes, I did
This, amazing, environment, right?
He's really buttering us up
N: This is Mashiro-san's profile!
"An attractive point you're confident about"
"Does not know fear"
That's right
I often do scary things on my streams, like horror games or reviewing supernatural photos
and I really like things like the occult and urban legends
Others would be like, "Gah! This is scary!"
But, I'm like, "I'm scared!" "I feel happy!"
It's like, "Positive things = scary"
Anything goes for you?
Like, what types of scary things...
I'm fine with anything. Anything!
Gory stuff..?
No problem
Painful-looking things...?
I'm totally fine with those
Monsters..?
What do the two of you consider scary?
What? He's turned the tables on us!
What, indeed
Monsters are scary. Psychic phenomena..
Ah, right, if things like poltergeists are suddenly about -- that's scary, right?
Aren't you gladabout that? ww
You're too happy about this!
The unknown is scary, right?
Things that you don't know. Things that are unknown are scary, right?
No, but that's wonderful. The very word 'unknown' is...
It's scary, but, isn't the word 'unknown' so nice?
Your diction! Your diction!
That's somewhat dodgy/spooky
In the first place, do you believe in ghosts and such?
No, I don't think they exist
You don't believe in them?
If I'm honest, I sort of wish they did
So you do those, horror type, streams because you're looking for those sorts of things?
That's right. I've used myself to experiment with a bunch of spiritual/necromancy techniques, but
nothing bad's ever happened to me!
Do you do those things because you want to figure out for yourself whether those things are real or not?
I do those things a lot, but, on the contrary, it's the people around me who become afflicted with misfortune
I'm jealous
It's enviable
Alright, next
How do you like to spend your days off?
Going to a family restaurant in the morning and enjoying the dirnk bar
while watching several films
This is really the best
Drink bars are really... They're impossible to dislike, right?
ww the drink bars are...
You can drink anything there, after all
Exactly! You can have cola, coffee, melon soda -- it's the best!
I realized this recently, but carbonated drinks are just..
both children and adults enjoy them. They're just the best, aren't they?!
So, while I drink -- Ah, yes! Better yet, in the morning! On a weekday!
When I look out the window, there's a bunch of salarymen and students looking tired and all
Meanwhile, I'm by myself, drinking cola, watching movies and reading manga! It's the best!
Is it different from drinking juice at home?
My house is rundown af, so I feel sad when I do that at home
Ah, so going to a family restaurant is important?
Just going to a family restaurant in itself makes me feel like I've spent my day meaningfully
What time do you get there?
I'm there from around 6AM to 12PM
That's early af!
I usually wake up around 9PM
9PM at night?
You wake up at 9PM?
I do
21 'o clock!
That's right!
Did you go today?
By the way, I did
You did?
Yeah, I just went there like I usually do
You relaxed gracefully before coming, huh..
TLN: Not familiar with movie genres. Seems about right.
By the way, I watched a depressing film
Ah, I'd hate that
Why did you watch a depressing film when we're recording today and need to keep the energy high?
Watching that genre is like, well..
When you watch a new movie, the unknown...
Like, what we just mentioned -- the experience of the unknown
It's simply that
So you were able to get excited from that?
Yeah
I thought, "After watching this, I can also go over to Yashiro's and have fun"
I'm double dipping!
That's perfect
I'm unexpectedly living an enjoyable life
I see
I completely forgot, but you guys brought souvenirs, didn't you?
Of course!
We did!
And what exactly is this...?
It's the other way around!
Cute!
Somehow, it's nice to have both of your poses
The gift I brought today was...
What I believe to be the tastiest candy in the world!
And that is... here!
Hi-Chew Premium Chewy Texture!
Your world's small...
No, but, they're tasty, right?
They are, but..
You're underestimating them, right? Have you tried them before?
Yeah
N: Well, of course
The're premium. Whatever you say about them, they're premium!
Aren't you weak to the word 'premium'?
Okay, the two of us will go first
They're good, aren't they?
It's Hi-Chew, that's for sure
Ah, while you still have a bit left in your mouth, try adding the lemon one as well
No way!
No, don't do it
Keeping them separate is definitely better
The taste of mixed Hi-Chew...
It'll definitely be delicious!
How is it?
Should I mix them?
Yes, mix them
Since the taste will change
All I taste is lemon
There's no way that's possible
It tastes like "lemon (grape)"
You see, you see
But, the other way around might have been better
Then, try the other way around
Ok, lemon first, right?
Well, they definitely taste good
But, lemon flavour gummies are really sour, right?
And to make it more mild, so that even children --
Wait a second, Akabane-san is...
She looks like it's really sour
It might be a bit sour..
Grape! Grape!
Spit it out immediately (?)
How is it?
I don't know what flavour this is
Right, you can't understand it!
It's premium!
That's no good!
This is what premium is!
Apologize to Morinaga!
Just what kind of performance will Mashiro show us?
He's entering the daipan circle!
According to my research,
it seemsl ike Mashiro will, "at any rate, challenge it while yelling."
I see. Then, Mashiro's daipan attempt, if you would!
There it is!
So, the result was 28.
Mashiro?
I didn't think I would get this kind of result...
Were you messing around?
Did you not mess around?
I put my all into it
Sorry, but didn't you say you were going to yell?
What happened to yelling?
I did it seriously...
With everything I had...
Certainly, the punch sounded dull
The point of impact was a bit..
It's strange, but, well..
That just means that this is how much power you have..
Everyone who supported me, I'm really sorry
Even I didn't imagine that I'd get this kind of result
With that, here is the current daipan ranking
That's it!
Draw a new creature that would appear in the Biohazard series!
I drew this as if I were paid by Biohazard to do so
It's doing a double peace sign
This is a shark centaur
This guy is amazing, you know?
It can do horseback archery
It can shoot arrows, and..
Once it gets close, it can eat you
Putting those two desires together,
this is the demonic beast that combines shark and centaur, the shark centaur