In the past, I've mentioned that my viewers
were about 90% male, 10% female, right?
Actually, recently, I've been playing Ark and Animal Gahering, so
my female viewer count increased! And, well..
My female viewership increased to a 7:1 male:female ratio!
However, did you guys know?
Ever since I started playing Yugioh, the male:female ratio of my viewers..
What do you think it is right now?
(My female viewers) increased! Thanks to Animal Gathering and Ark.
The correct answer is, well, right now...
99.1% male
0.9% female
Isn't that crazy?
Ahhh, give them back to me!
Return my cute female viewers!
Where did you all go?
Give them back to me!
But, well, this [Yugioh] is fun, so it can't be helped
[My] enjoyment and women.. it's that, you know?
It's a balancing act, surely
To obtain something enjoyable, you have to give up something else
For me, well..
Even though I was supposed to take good care of women..
now, all I'm left with are Yugioh-loving old men
Let's get along, everybody!
Let's get along from now on, as well
But, if a girl does show up among you, please treat her gently
Honestly, to be honest --
Even when I previously said I had very few female viewers,
Even then, I had about 1%
I had 1% back then, but, now.. no longer...
Where did those girls go?
Those girls..
I realized that it doesn't matter if my viewers are male or female
What's important is, you know, it doesn't matter who it is,
It doesn't matter who, as long as I can make a large number of people happy,
that's the most important thing of all, I think.
Let's flirt with girls, at least in a game. This much is fine.
Female... 0.1%...