Sakura Miko (M)
Hololive
Hoshimachi Suisei (S)
Context: they each went on a website that makes joke resumé-like 'diagnoses' (診断書) and will share them with each other.
I didn't get to see Miko-chan's...
I saw Sui-chan's ww
Right, Miko saw mine, right?
There were quite a lot of horrible things written on my diagnosis ww
Oh, listen, I really wanted to talk about this
We tried doing some sort of 'personality resumé'
Please take a look, everyone
I sort of feel sorry
It kind of feels like the real thing
First off, this is what it looks like
Let's do one half at a time
TLN: No worries, you'll see
a translation of all of this shortly.
First off is the resumé, right
Personality resume
Family name: Sui chan
Age of vitality: 6 y.o. // masculine, feminine
Time period | Rundown of activities
Elementary school: Took control of surroundings.
Full of self-confidence.
Middle school: Didn't study at all, but was peaceful.
High school: Played  around a lot. Things were stable.
So, "Hoshimachi Suisei"
We're going to have a look at your personality resumé
Ok, have at it
Family name - "Sui-chan"
"Age of vitality"
"Age of vitality"?
First off, what does "Age of vitality" even mean? - is what I thought
"Age of vitality" ww
What's "age of vitality"? I'm 18 y.o., for the record
You're... 16 y.o., aren't you?
Hmm... seems like I'm 16 y.o.
Well, it's nice that you're young
Yeah, I have nothing against that
About whether you're masculine or feminine..
You were feminine!
Well, that's about right. I'm a girl, after all
Moving on to the "Rundown of activities,"
In elementary school, you took control and were full of confidence. Is that true?
Yeahh, it really was like that
In elementary school, I was really hyper
I had a bit of an early chuunibyou phase, around 6th grade or so
TLN: chuunibyou, 中二病, literally, "8th grade illness." tl;dr being a cringe weeb
What was it like?
Well, honestly.. I had memorized spell chants
from Bleach and went around saying them all the time
"Ye lord! Mask of blood and flesh, all creation, flutter of wings, ye who bears the name of Man! Inferno and pandemonium, the sea barrier surges, march on to the South!"
TLN: "君臨者よ！血肉の仮面·万象·羽ばたき·ヒトの名を冠す者よ！ 焦熱と争乱、海隔て逆巻き南へと歩を進めよ！"
I said that in the classroom, that one..
I can imagine you doing that! ww
I see! So, it was just like how it's written here
Exactly
In middle school, you didn't study at all, but things were peaceful.
You didn't study, huh?
I didn't - in elementary school, I studied a lot, and
There's something called 'self-study"
Like, for homework, we had to write
however many pages in our self-study notebook each day.
Everybody hated it, so
even though I self-studied a lot in elementary school,
once I became a middle schooler,
due to becoming weeb (getting into anime/manga)
I stopped studying
That happens pretty commonly, right?
My grades dropped
BUUUT.. it was a peaceful middle school experience
Well, I get not having studied
I get it, I get it
Right?
You get hooked on anime and such around that time, right?
Right, right
I stopped studying around that time, so I became
unable to speak English. Not good.
Everyone's going, "That happens."
Isn't that right, everybody?
Say, "Twitter!" "Twitter"
Please tweet on Twitter because the chat is broken, thank you
Right,
please tweet "micomet" on "Twitter"
Next, high school: "Played around a lot, but things were stable."
Yup, high school was, you know?
I.. played around a lot
I say 'play,' but, I don't mean the 'wild' kind of playing
TLN: ブイブイ; ie very outgoing, sociable, etc. Stuff like parties, etc.
I was up to my neck, grinding away in otaku activities
Well, I'm still in high school now, but..
A "Sazae-san"-like high schooler..
TLN: "Sazae-san" is the longest running  anime.
That's right. It's an infinite loop, right?
Right, right
During my 3rd year of high school, however many years ago,
Well, like, I had so many absences
that a teacher told me, "If you're absent much more, you're not going to able to graduate, you know?"
That's pretty insane ww
Yeah, I was told that, but..
then, I asked, "Well then, how many more absences can I have before I'm unable to graduate?"
because I wanted to know where the cutoff was.
Then, they said, "Hmm.. if you're absent about 5 more times, you won't be able graduate."
So, I was like, "5 times, huh.."
ww "then, how about four more.."
Exactly! I was like, "Let's take four more days off.."
And, you know, if you're late -- if you don't arrive until noon,
If you do that three times,
that was treated as once absence.
So, I was like, "Ok, let's just go to school at noon."
I often went to school around noon
That happens when you're in your third (last) year
Exactly, that's what when you're a third-year
Like, when it's close to graduation
Right, right
So, I played around a lot, but, well..
I was able to accomplish what I wanted to do,
so I think there was a sense of stability
Yes, well.. Certainly, that's what stability would be.. yup.
To each their own when it comes to graduating, and, moving on,
Rewards and punishments.
- Wearing a short skirt while riding a bike. Fine: 200$
- Watching YouTube while studying.
Penalty: 1 year of forced labour.
- Not seeing various things to completion. Fine: 100$
- Immediately forgetting passwords. Fine: 300$
- Having optimistically naive thoughts and resolution.
Fine: 300$
Next, there's a section called, "Rewards and Punishment"
You're pretty... what is it..
From the top,
"Riding a bike while wearing a short skirt" ww
".. and making something rustle." (TLN: as in, her skirt)
About this fine, though..
I don't recall doing this!
They just arbitrarily assumed -- like, "You've done this before, haven't you?"
This is totally biased!
Unforgivable
But it's something I can picture you doing
Is that so?
".. made something rustle." What are they referring to?
Something like, my underwear was nearly visible?
But, I properly weared spats underneath my skirt, so
there's no way my skirt would move around like that
So, it wasn't openly visible
Well, that's how it is
But, were your skirts short?
No, not really, well..
I didn't care at all about skirt length
I thought that long skirts could be cute as well, but..
I received a skirt from someone
Ah, one that had already been cut?
TLN: If you weren't aware, Japanese students have a long history of modifying their uniforms, e.g. elongating or trimming skirts.
Exactly! And, it was a just a bit small
So a teacher pulled me over and said, "Hey, you shortened your skirt, didn't you?"
TLN: The teacher is using fairly coarse language. Imagine Onizuka from GTO.
Then, I was like, "Huh? I didn't, foo"
TLN: Suisei's also using a rude tone
"You're breaking rules, a rule-breaker. You broke the rules!"
"What, I didn't shorten my skirt!" -- and a fight broke out
That's so scary! You were a delinquent!
You had that kind of attitude towards your teacher?
"Hey, you just tried to falsely accuse me, didn't you, mofo?!"
"You don't have anything to say to me?"
Scary! I'd definitely not want to become your teacher!
I really got into fights with my teacher
I had a really bad relationship with them
You were a problem child, weren't you
Next, "the crime of watching YouTube while studying."
"1 year of penal labour"
Well, you'd definitely watch, right
Yeah, I did
Well, I didn't actually watch YouTube that much
since, if I were found out, it'd be annoying
But... I drew pictures, right? During class
I drew pictures while in class, and
when things were troublesome,
I'd tell another girl, "Tell them that I've gone to the infirmary (nurse's room),"
and then, I'd just shut myself in the toilet
and completely immerse myself in social games
In the toilet (??)
TLN: Couldn't pick up the rest
Yeah, I played social games on the toilet
next, "the crime of not seeing things through to completion."
Yeah, I get called a jack of all trades..
TLN: 器用貧乏
You can really hide your crimes, here though (?)
There's nothing but crime here, though ww
But, I don't have a single thing mastered. Alright, next.
No, you have! If I had to say, I think you give that impression.
But, you know, as a result of trying out a lot of different
things that I like or want to do,  I haven't been able to
master any. I think there may be some truth to that.
Is that right? Yet, you're this good at Tetris
Actually, even with Tetris, I haven't fully mastered it, you know
Is that so?
Yeah
Even with how good you are now? You'd beat me up, you know?
Well, yeah, I'd definitely beat you up ww
What's with that..
Next, "the crime of immediately forgetting your password"
Yeah, this one's right. I forget them.
You do?!
Yeah
"The crime of having optimistically naive thoughts and resolution."
Ehh.. certainly, I might think optimistically
That's right
The crime of having half-baked determination...
I don't think it fits you
That's a pretty horrible thing to say, right? "Your resolution is weak."
It's like something an annoying manager would say
"Your resolution is weak, huh."
That's a crime, it is.
Annoying, really.
Qualifcations and Certifications
- Inspiration Exam Level 2
- Spiritual Certification Level 3
- Friendship Development Practitioner, Level 3
- Brain-off Certification Level 2
- Clout chaser, Level 3
- "Bad for the environment? None of my business"
Certificate, Level 1
- Flawed Logic Certification, Level 2
- Chatterbox Certification, Level 3
Next, we have a "Qualifications and Certifications" section
I'll read it
Inspiration exam level 2
Spiritualcertification level 3
Friendship development practitioner level 3
Brain-off certification, level 2
clout chaser level 3
"Bad for the planet? Not my business." Level 1
What does this mean? Really..
Apologize to the Earth!
This is horrible~
There's no such thing!
I buy eco-bags, though
TLN: I heard 地袋, but I think it's something like an eco-bag? not sure.
Flawed logic level 2
Chatterbox level 3
That's a good thing, right?
This is probably why I'm called an extrovert, this "chatterbox certification."
You're definitely an extrovert ww
So that was the 'resume' we had..
And, on the other side, we have the personality part
That's the main part, okay?
Personality summary:
Fairly popular. Doesn't stiffen up when meeting
people. Sense of duty is a tad lacking.
It's the main, right
Okay, I'll read it
First off,
"Personality summary"
"Fairly popular. Doesn't stiffen up when meeting people."
"Sense of duty is a tad lacking."
A tad lacking..
Well, well..
Common events in their life
- Immediately points out when people stage
photos to make their legs look longer.
- Kind, but doesn't really carry any burdens.
- When people are singing, immediately jumps
in during the interlude or as harmony.
- Their material desires are amazing.
- Disgusting way of eating grilled fish.
- If asked for opinions on movies and such, only
ever respond with something like "It was good."
- Adventurous and aggressive fashion.
- Quickly admires people who aren't any special
"Common events in their life"
"Immediately points out when people stage photos to make their legs look longer."
"Kind, but doesn't really carry any burdens."
"When people are singing, immediately joins in during the interlude or as harmony."
I wouldn't!
This is so arbitrary!
This is really... ww
"Their material desires are amazing"
"Disgusting way of eating grilled fish."
They're not!
That's horrible!
"When asked for their opinions on movies and such,"
"they only ever respond with something like, It was good."
Stop it~!
"Adventurous and aggressive fashion."
It's not aggressive!
"Quickly comes to admire people who aren't anything special."
That's a good thing, right?
That's a good thing ww
It's a good thing
This might be the only good trait here ww
Really, this is horrible
But, honestly, the first one..
It's true
I can picture it -- "This person.. wait a second.."
I really do immediately point it out
"They're faking it"
"These people, they're definitely doing something, right?"
But, there are people like that
Like, if you look at Korean fashion sites, they do this a lot
Is that right?
I had no idea!
That so?
They make their legs look way, way longer, and
they may even make them look thinner, too
Ah, but don't they say, like..
you won't notice if they distort the background (to match).
Yeah, they do that.
And, as a result, you don't know what length skirt to buy,
so when you buy one, it's often the wrong size.
I've also had, like, ..
"Ah, this skirt looks cute!" But when I order it,
I'm like, "Woah, this is a super mini skirt."
I ordered it thinking, "Damn, is this miniskirt going to be too flashy?"
It didn't even match the length of my legs
That's cringe ww
So I'm like, "Really?"
That happens, right?
It does
Yeah, so I immediately point that out
Likes: Height and self-actualization; organics;
when needed, strong eyedrops; dance; vivid colours;
Halloween; hats; musicals; festivals; dollar stores;
Dislikes: time before an exam; washroom cleaning;
fussy men; planning personalities; "Your outfit looks
cold"; old men; how unimpressive photos get popular;
people who don't say what they think; working out
Alright, next, "Likes"!
"Height and self-actualization."
"Organics"
"Strong eyedrops"
"Vivid colours."
"Halloween, hats, musicals."
"Festivals. Dollar stores."
These are largely correct
These are fairly accurate, huh
Well, I don't know about "strong eyedrops"
That'd be too hardcore
True. Eyedrops don't have that strong an effect
"Dislikes. Time before an exam. Washroom cleaning. Fussy men."
"Planning personality types. The phrase, 'Your outfit looks cold.' "
"How unimpressive photos become popular. People who don't say what they think. Exercise."
I thought that these would be accurate
"Your outfit looks cold~!"
You'd just be like, "Huh?"
Well, it depends on who's saying it
If it were a friend - "Aren't you cold in that?"
I'd just say, "No, this is unexpectedly warm, actually."
But if I were told, "Your outfit looks cold," by someone I'm not that close with,
"Ha?"
Scary ww
That's how it is
No, but, I get it
It's a matter of fashion
Exactly
Like, "Shut up"
And, let's see, what else seems accurate..
Additionally, "People who don't say what they think" is fairly accurate, I think
But, if people are being equivocal out of politeness --
TLN: オブラートに包む. From 'oblaat.'
I am a delicate person, so I want people to be indirect, but..
Like, for example, if someone was asked, "How about hanging out tomorrow?"
and they went, "Sorry, I have plans with another person."
"Sorry! I really wanted to go, though! Sorry!"
If they actually had nothing to do,
I would prefer it if, rather than saying all that..
That's true
Just be like, "Ah, I'm sleepy. Lazy."
"I'm feeling a bit sleepy, you know?"
That's true
I'd like people who could say that
It's easier that way, right
Right, right
How to handle. If my attitude seems conceited,
please overlook it. I like interacting with people, so,
if you could reach out proactively. If you get to
know me, I'll probably seem interesting, so
please draw that out of me.
Next, "How to handle (me)"
"If my attitude seems conceited, please let that go."
That's seems about right ww
"I like interacting with people, so if you could reach out proactively." [sic]
"If you get to know me, I'll probably seem interesting, so please draw that out of me."
It isn't a big deal, though.
But, you know, my high school teacher always said to me,
"Hoshimachi, you know, you're really conceited af."
"Huh? You're annoying, you know!"
Conceited? ww
Yeah, like, "You're looking down on us."
How many times was I told that?
"What part of me* makes you think I'm looking down on you?"
I got into a lot of fights
The teacher must have been on the verge of throwing hands
Your teacher definitely didn't like you
Yeah, he didn't
Like, "Really?!"
Like, "How tf you going around with that attitude towards your teacher?"
That's how it'd go, right
Exactly
That's right. That's the truth
Personal request entry field. I'm certainly a
suspicious person, but please do not interrogate
me. Even if I'm trying to get a laugh out of someone,
please understand that I'm just going with the flow.
Please do not wear the same outfit. Please do
not expect anything from me. I'm actually quite
vulgur, so please forgive me. I'd like my
birthday to be celebrated, so please do so.
Apparently
"Personal request entry field."
"I'm certainly a suspicious person, but please do not interrogate me."
I'm not suspicious
"Even if I'm trying to get a laugh, please understand that I'm just going with the flow."
"Please do not wear the same outfit."
"Please do not expect anything from me."
"I'm actually quite vulgar, so please forgive me."
"I want my birthday to be celebrated, so please do so."
My true desires are written here, though~
There's a lot of bias in here, though ww
They really took the piss on you
Yeah, they're shitting on me
But, you know, I can recognize a slight trace of Sui-chan (in the text)
Why? Am I being exposed?
You are
Where?
"I'm certainly a suspicious person, but please don't question me."
I'm not suspicious!
"Even if I'm trying to get a laugh, please understand that I'm only going with the flow."
That's true.
It really is just my energy and going with the flow
Quite a few of these hit the mark, don't they?
Quite a few do, yeah
Currently lacking - life philosophy and deep thinking.
Currently in excess. - people who are on the
level of, "I recognize that face."
Thickness of the wall between people on the
first encounter: thin.
One word descriptor: unrealistic
That's troubling
Let's see
"One word descriptor." It says "unrealistic."
What does that mean, I wonder
Right?
It's troublesome to look into it, so..
I don't know this word, after all
You don't?
No, I don't know
The meaning of "unrealistic"?
If you're going to say that, look up what it means!
"Unlikely to happen in reality. Unrealistic. Fantastical."
So it says.
So that was Sui-chan's resume.
Yes, that was my resume
Then, let's see Mikocchi's!
Noooo~