Honma
Himawari
H: Then, let's begin the graduation ceremony.
Kuzuha
Yamiyono
Moruru
Makaino
Ririmu
Sasaki
Saku
Yuika
Shiina
Setsuna
H: Sasaki Saku-san, congratulations on your graduation.
S: Thank you
H: Yes, let's see..
H: In regards to Sasaki Saku's graduation, we have received messages and emails
H: from several people who aren't here today.
H: So, I'd like to read them out.
H: With that, Shiina-chan, if you will.
(Shiina) SH: Yes.
H: Please come to the stage.
SH: This is a message from Akabane-san.
SH: "To Sacchan."
Do you remember who I am?
It's Akabane Youko.
We were able to chat briefly just before the academic ability test, right?
The slightly timid way you laughed was so cute that
even now, I remember the sound of your laugh.
At the time, I wasn't thinking at all about
how it would be our first and last [voice] call.
When I think about how, from now on, the Gamers will
gather like we have today
and get excited over games,
to be honest, it makes me sad.
As our group never had that many people in it,
each and every member's existence was cherished and important.
And the space we have created cannot be filled by anyone else.
The empty seat that Sacchan will leave behind will remain vacant from now on, so
No, honestly, when I first heard of this, I cried.
I cried, felt down, and, finally, I became able to send you off with a smile, so
"Congratulations on your graduation."
Go on a worldwide rampage, Sasaki!
I'm rooting for Sacchan's dreams.
If we ever meet, please give me your signature.
Sorry for being absent for our Minecraft collaboration.
You will be watching over us from Heaven, so
please enjoy watching the Gamers to your heart's content along with all our listeners.
From Akabane Youko.
That's all
Kuzuha (K): I, too..
K: I have a message from Kanae-kun
K: Is it alright?
S: Please
K: Um.. so, this is from Kanae
"Dear Sasaki,"
First off, thank you very much for the last four months.
I did not play very much with Sasaki on-stream, but
your streams were interesting, so I watched them here and there.
In our Mario Tennis collaboration, results-wise, I wasn't able to win, but it was still a lot of fun.
I won't be able to have my revenge, but that in itself seems like it will become a good memory.
Personally, I am really fond of the sound you make when chewing on cookies.
TLN: 咀嚼音
Your crunching was really something, wasn't it?
It was short time, but I'm glad that we managed to accomplish many different things.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please contact me anytime if there's ever an opportunity for me to help with something you want to do.
I'll lend a hand as long as it's something I can do.
As the seasons are changing, please take care of your health to not fall ill.
Please properly take care of yourself from now on.
Until we meet again.
P.S. This is the last time anyway, so I'd appreciate it if you changed how you refer to me.
K: That's all.
S: Thank you.
H: Thank you very much
H: Then, next..
H: Ririmu, if you would.
Ririmu (R): Yes.
S: Are you alright?
H: It's alright, Ririmu.
K: Please take your time.
Farewell...
"Dear 「Sasaki Saku yo~」-san,"
Regarding your leaving Nijisanji Gamers, it will be lonely, but
please put everything you have into achieving what you want to do.
I want you to have confidence in your decisions so that you have no regrets.
Also, please give the underwater exploration game Subnautica a try - it's really good.
R: That's it.
H: Thank you very much
S: Thank you
H: With that...
H: Then, genmate Moru-chan, if you would.
Moruru (M): Sorry, my voice is a little dead right now, but..
H: Ah, wait, sorry. Just wait a moment
H: Before that, let's hear from everyone individually.
H: Let's start with Shiina-chan, if you would.
H: You can do it from there.
SH: Joining Gamers.. the mere fact that Sasaki Saku was there..
SH: Honestly, it made me really happy..
SH: Also, when I was just starting out,
SH: I was doing things on my own,
SH: and, when I was wondering whether I should approach things more freely,
SH: Sasaki told me, "Even if you get out of hand, I will still collab with you."
SH: I vividly remember that.
SH: And, when things were really tough and I was thinking of quitting,
SH: even when I hadn't said anything, she immediately called me
SH: Like, I couldn't say it, but, more... I have a lot of regrets
SH: like, "I should have stopped her from retiring," but...
SH: now, I'm at the point where I can forget about all of that, because
SH: I want her to be happy and enjoy her life from now on
SH: That's all.
S: Thank you
H: Thank you very much
H: Then, next, Ririmu, if you would.
R: Yes.
R:  Shasha and I did not interact on-stream at all, but
R: She was really, really thoughtful towards me off-stream.
R: She heard me out whenever I was worried about streaming and such.
R: Like, I was worried about how bad my mic was
R: When I was worried about my mic, Shasha gave me her's.
R: And, we've also went out to eat together.
R: From now on, as part. of.. Gamers...
R: as part of Nijisanji..
R: Shasha won't be able to get along with us where everyone can see, which is sad, but
R: But! From now on, I want to continue getting along with Shasha!
R: Was that okay?
H: It was.
H: Thank you
S: Thank you
H: Thank you very much
H: Next, um..
H: Setsuna-san can't talk right now, but, later, via chat or something..
H: Next, Kuzuha, if you would.
K: Yes.
K:  I first learned of Sasaki from a Splatoon video, but
K: that was my first time seeing her, and
K: I thought, "She's insanely good!" I really respect people who are good at games, so..
K: Since then, I always thought that I'd like to try interacting with her
K: But, since I'm not proactive with reaching out for collabs and such,
K: and a lot's happened, such that, as of today, we still haven't collabed..
K: Honestly, that's really frustrating
K: I'm also thinking, "You've never even collabed, so what's with you?", but..
K: I was really shocked when I first heard, to the point that
K: even I was surprised by how I reacted.
K: It was, like, unexpected.
K: If I could say something really selfish,
K: it's to the point that I want to shout, "Sakaki, don't quit!"
K: But.. I wanted to keep going together as part of Gamers.
K: This is something that Sasaki decided on after deep consideration..
K: At the same time, I'm also hoping that there's a path where you can continue as a liver
K: But, even after you graduate from Nijisanji, I'll always support you.
K: Please do your best. Really, thank you very much.
K: And, anytime... if you return..
K: We'll give you a grand welcome, so..
K: Thank you very much
H: Thank you very much
H: Then, genmate Moru-chan, if you would
M: Yes.
M: My voice is difficult to listen to, but..
M: Dear Saku-chan,
M: Since we began our activities in July, it's been about four months.
M: It was brief, but I am very glad we were able to work together.
M: I really love how you gently compliment others.
TLN: I'm sorry, I really can't understand her voice well right now
M: From now on, please stay as you are.
M: It makes me very sad that this is the last time you collab with us as part of Gamers..
M: I am truly very grateful.
M: I will always support what you want to do.
M: Thank you very much
S: Thank you
H: Thank you very much
H: Then, lastly, genmate Himawari..
K: Go ahead.
H: Yes.
H: I still remember how excited we were when our debut dates were confirmed
H: At that time, four of us -- Sorry, just a minute..
H: This was wrong ww
H: Dear Saku-chan, once again,
H: Congratulations on your graduation
H: Was it around May when I first learned of Saku-chan?
H: Even now, I still remember how excited I was upon
H: hearing that you were a girl who likd aquariums and Nintendo.
H: Afterwards, Ririmu invited us all into a voice call
H: That was the first time Saku-chan, Ririmu, and I talked, right?
H: The sound quality and many other things were so bad that it made us laugh really hard, right?
H: And then, Moru also joined, and we had so much fun that we kept talking until the next morning, right?
H: Once our debut dates were decided, we were really excited
H: At that time, the four of us said, "If any of us ever have any trouble, let's help each other out."
H: I believe that the support of those words helped everyone to debut without issue.
H: We all watched each other's debut streams, and,
H: afterwards, we gathered in Discord and complimented each other, right?
H: Since then, it's been four months, right?
H: We had many different collabs. It was fun, wasn't it?
H: In these past four months, fun things, sad things, surprising things,
H: a lot has happened, right?
H: And, every time, we would all gather to talk, right?
H: Looking back, I was only ever acting spoiled towards Saku-chan, wasn't I?
H: I'm sorry for going up to you and saying, "No! Stop it! I'll be lonely!"
H: But, after hearing what you had to say, I've come to feel supportive of you
H: It's not like we can't meet each other after you graduate
H: And we can still talk.
H: So, it'll definitely be alright.
H: If things become difficult, please reach out to me anytime.
H: EVEN IF things become difficult, please reach out anytime, okay?
H: I'll be waiting, okay?
H: To the cool Sasaki Saku. From, Honma Himawari.
S: Thank you.
H: Yes.
H: Yes
H: Then, Sasaki Saku-san, please come up to the stage.
S: Yes
H: Then, I'll hand this over to you
H: Here you go
S: Oh, amazing!
S: Wow, you can do something like this
K: It's got proper writing on it.
M: What's written on it?
S: "Congratulations on your graduation. We wish that our beloved Saku-chan
S: will be able to freely enjoy continuing your activities
S: Please return anytime, okay?
S: "Gamers."
S: Thank you
K: Really, please return anytime
H: Come back~!
H: I love you, Saku-chan!
S: I'm really sorry..
H: It's okay..
S: Thank you..
R: Thank you, too.
H: Thank you..