Shigure Ui
Hoshimachi
Suisei
Alright, then,
I did a preliminary survey about Sui-chan
I found out who your oshis are
Yes!
Ah, crap!
I know you like this person, so --
look at your screen!
I put it beside you!
EH?! I really like this person, though!
Mess up! Mess up!
I really, really like her, though!
I want to put another one, but..  !
But, right now, I can't.. !
Damn! Do you know who this is?
TLN: Promare, I believe
Rio-san, right?
That's right!
I went to watch the movie!
You did?!
I really, really like her!
I knew, I knew!
Damn.. so one wasn't enough, huh?
Then, how about we bring out one more?
Yes.
Then, beside you, here's another.. I just drew it..
I put it beside you, please have a look!
It's Takakagi Kaede, who I like!
Do you like her?
Please mess up!
I like her so much, she brings tears to my eyes
Oh, really? ww
Do you know Takakagi Kaede?
I do, she's the
She likes alcohol and puns, right?
Yes! I really like that she's really good at singing,  yet
She's good, huh?
But, well, she likes telling sleazy jokes
I really like that mischievous part about her!
That's good, keep that up
You're doing well
That's good, getting distracted?
She's cute, right?
She's cute, very cute!
Oh, and, she's really tall!
How tall?
Over 170cm!
That's ta~ll
Right?
crap crap crap
Actually, I really like girls who are taller than 170cm
*sigh*
Go on.. ?
Yeah, well, cool beauties are nice, aren't they?
Does Sui-chan like cool beauties?
Yes, I like cool beauties
Is that so? I see
I like cool beauties, and
Aren't you fast?
I like.. that.. young boys
Oh! I've heard of that!
Not sho*ta*s, but shou*nen*s, right?
That's right
If I talk about shotas,
I might be able to distract Sui-chan, but my image would suffer
So I should be careful
is what Sui-chan's listeners told me
That's right
crap crap crap
That's no good. It's not shotas
In fact, I think of Rio as a shounen
Ahh.. Certainly, her voice is quite low, right?
Yeah, her voice is quite deep, right?
Are you distracted at all?
To be honest, I am making mistakes
I've been making a lot of mistakes
That right.. I can't shake your mental with just Rio et al., is that it?
That... may be so..
What should I do?
hmph, I see
Ah, then. I thought of it
I've come up with my next tactic already
What?
You see, it is..
Shigure Ui will retreat.
Farewell.
Huh, she disappeared
Shigure! Shigure~!
Sui-chan? Sui-chan? It's a shounen
What are you laughing about?
I'm a shounen, you know?
What's so funny?
Hey, let's go
Eh? This is really up my alley
Let's go
Hey, let's do it
I really like this!
Let's start!
I really like this
True? That's nice
Let's go.
I really like the look of your eyes
I like how you look a little twisted
but also have a soft side
Nothing's twisted here
By the way, I've talked with Sui-chan before
No way, really?
Over the phone.
You forgot. You completely forgot
Painful.
Even though it was so fun
So fast! She's not disturbed at all!
Crap! Wait up!
I really like you/your voice
Hey, hey, if you like it, hold back a bit
Ah, then.. should I hold back a bit?
Then, maybe I'll hold back a little?
Wait, wait, I don't have anywhere to put this!
Save me!
Maybe I'll hold back?
Save me, please
So your name's Uio-kun?
That's right
I am... Uio
What do you like?
What are your hobbies?
My hobbies are.. high school girls and.. ah
I got a bit flustered~
Ah, I.. like high school girls
You like high school girls?
How old's Sui-chan?
Sui-chan's in.. www ... high school
Nice! I like you, Hoshimachi
I was so confused that I made a mistake ww
I like you, Hoshimachi.. !
Somehow, he likes me!
But, well, I don't particularly want to be liked by young boys
What is it..
What do you want from young boys?
I want to watch them
You know, well, young boys are in their puberty, right?
So to speak
I guess so?
Yeah, so, I want to watch the unique period
of puberty when all kinds of things happen to them
Hmm.. that's so similar to Shigure Ui's attitude towards
high school girls that I can't say anything back
I have nothing to say. I get it.
You get it, right?
Totally.
I don't want to be involved with them, honestly
Ah, it's the end, huh?
There's one more, you know?
Oh, one more?
There is.
So I can keep talking with Uio-kun?!
That's right. Talk to me about anything
What about high school girls does Uio-kun like?
The transience, so to speak, like, well,
there's only 2 to 3 years, right?
The boundary between being children
and adults is really nice, isn't it?
We're totally the same, aren't we?!
That's it! I get it! That's exactly it!
It's the transience of it, you know?
That's what I'm looking for!
It's that short period of time when
you're neither a child nor an adult,
that's what so good --- !!
Yes, yes, yes!
Goodbye-ui...
Huh, Uio-kun?
Uio died.
Ah! It's Ui-chan
That's no good,
if you make me bring out Uio-kun!
You're supposed to get distracted!